they have to walk
han deandar una
something It's going to be a mess
cosa Se va a liar
eh it's going to be a mess tagged Fran
eh se va a liar etiquetado Fran
tagged Fran because I know it's going to be a
etiquetado Fran porque sé que se va a
mess
liar
wc new pet how do we
wc nueva mascota cómo le
name it
ponemos
mother of
madre del amor
beautiful love mother of beautiful love no no no no
hermoso madre del amor
that kid no he's not
no que ese chaval
civilized
no no está civilizado
no he's not
no no está
civilized it's a black sopilote very
civilizado es un sopilote negro muy
common here but it's very common to
comunes aquí pero es muy comúnes
keep it on a
llevarlo con
leash it's very common to keep it on a
Correa es muy común llevarlo con
leash mother of the
Correa madre de la
amm
amm
but I mean I understand that it's a bird that
pero o sea entiendo que es un pájaro que
is very common there but in a
que es muy común allí pero en plan
free plan I mean it's a wild
libre o sea es un animal libre salvaje
free animal Not from the Forest I imagine We're already losing viewers yeah sayayina things are really bad sayaya that's why Become a member Become a member Frank will be in the chat Well I don't think it will take long as soon as he sees the tweet that I posted I don't think it will take long to
puesto no creo que tarde mucho en
appear
aparecer
but it's that Apart from uploading the photo
pero es que ya Aparte ya subir la foto
No wcol already responded
No ya respondió
Where wcol responded to
wcol En dónde respondió wcol a
that
eso
Oh that W since W already responded and that he
Ah que W ya que W ya respondió y que
said it was a meme that they have funned her
dijo que era un meme que la han funado
in all the okay come on okay
en todos los vale venga vale
places send it to me Lu come on you me  you
lugares mándamelo Lu venga tú me lo
send it now I'm going to try to Meanwhile I'm
mandas ahora voy a tratar de Mientras
going to try to while another I'm going to
voy a tratar de mientras otro voy a
try to while another topic that just
tratar de mientr otro tema que acaba de
exploded on Twitter too and and I think it's
explotar en Twitter también y y creo que
funny to see it turns out
es divertido a ver resulta ser
that these gachon these hornets are not the
que estos gachon estos cachondos no a
ones who like to stir up the hornets' nest
los que le gusta mover el avispero
when I wake up in the morning they
cuando me levanto por la mañana me
send me the following clip for me to
mandan el siguiente clip para que yo lo
tweet it okay Comanche hasn't held
twitee vale Comanche no se ha cortado un
back in insulting the
pelo en insultar al
moror and he said the following he's a
moror y ha dicho lo siguiente es un
piece of [ __ ] who insults from
pedazo de [__] que insulta desde
Andorra because there nobody can do
andorra porque allí nadie le puede hacer
anything to him but when you meet him on the
nada pero cuando te lo encuentras por la
street he's not able to hold your
calle no es capaz de mantenerte la
gaze a Comanche clip from one of his
mirada clip de Comanche de uno de sus
last live shows okay it seemed to me like
últimos directos vale a mí me ha parecio
a good little jump the truth is that I have
un buen salcito la verdad es que yo he
agreed with these people in
estado de acuerdo con esta gente en
tweeting Okay and and I have put it the truth is
twitear Vale y y lo he puesto la verdad
I thought it was a good clip we have put
me ha parecido buen clip le hemos puesto
our little things no and we have found a
nuestras cositas no y nos ha aparecido
good clip
buen clip
to the moror the moror the moror doesn't deserve
al moror el moror el moror no se merece
a [ __ ] song The moror is [ __ ]
una [__] canción El moror es una [__]
people do you think that I am going to waste
gente ustedes creen que yo voy a gastar
my vocal cords in making a song
mis cuerdas vocales en hacer una canción
to  that piece of
a esa pedazo de [__]
human [ __ ] he is the lowest that exists
humana el es lo más bajo que existe
brother
hermano
M he is a daddy's mommy's boy locked up
M es un niñito de mami de papi encerrado
in Andorra throwing [ __ ] from Andorra
en andorra tirando [__] desde andorra
because there nobody can do anything to him the
porque ahí nadie le puede hacer nada el
[ __ ] I
cabrón o
mean in Andorra there is no street or what is the
sea en andorra no hay calle o cómo es la
movement to verendo like I understand Well of course in
movida a verendo entiendo Bueno claro en
Andorra be careful eh with delineating there
andorra cuidado eh con delinir allí
eh in Andorra be careful with delineating there
eh en andorra cuidado con delinir allí
Eh already I know look I've seen it I've
Eh ya ya sé mira ya lo he visto ya lo he
seen it that's why we are commenting on it and if
visto por eso estamos comentándolo y si
you run into him on the street The [ __ ] Or
te lo encuentras en la calle Al cabrón O
you run into him in I don't know when I ran into him
te lo encuentras en yo que sé cuando me
a verada deb had thrown
lo encontré una verada deb había tirado
[ __ ] and he lowers his head [ __ ] you
[__] y agacha la cabeza cabrón lo
turn to look at him like this to see if he gives you
volteas a ver así para ver si te tira
a frontal look adora or something and he lowers his
una mirada fronte adora o algo y agacha
head
cabeza
but anyways even if this were
pero de todas maneras aunque esto fuera
true Look, I'm not with El
verdad A ver aquí no estoy yo con El
Comanche at all eh I mean really
Comanche para nada eh o sea realmente
even if it were
aunque fuera
true if you have something to debate with
verdad si tú tienes algo que debatir con
someone or something to
alguien o algo que
discuss if you have something to discuss
discutir si tienes algo que discutir
argue with your arguments no I mean
discute con tus argumentos no O sea que
you're supposed to look at someone to see if they
que tú miras a alguien para ver si te
look at you  I mean but that was from the
mira o sea pero eso era de de la
movie seven virgins not like a
película de siete vírgenes no en plan un
little chauvinist no a little
poco de cani no un poco
of what of I mean how's the move I mean I
de de de qué de o sea cómo es la movida
look at you and if you answer me the
o sea yo te miro y si tú me respondes la
look directly adoring No what is it that you
mirada fronte adora No qué es lo que
do
hacéis os
hit each other what do you think is worth throwing at that that
pegá qué creen que vale la pena tirarle
piece of [ __ ] no no it's not worth it
ese ese pedazo de [__] no no no vale
people Oh oh oh okay Okay Okay Eh
la pena gente Ay ay ay okay Okay Okay Eh
let's see let's see let's see let's see let's see
vamos a ver vamos a ver vamos a ver a
Well according to El Comanche
ver a ver Bueno pues según El Comanche
the goat the goat according to El Comanche
la cabra el goat según El Comanche
eh looked at the dude at an event to see
eh miró a el moror en un evento para ver
if the dude was looking at him but of course I
si el moror le miraba pero claro
understand that if he looks back at him he's not
entiendo que si le devuelve la mirada no
inviting him to dinner I understand that he's
lo invita a cenar entiendo que está
insinuating like a
insinuando como una
fight
pelea no
eh And the
eh Y el
dude doesn't give a damn okay
moror me
handsome the best one just
vale vale guapo el millor acaba de
tweeted This
twitear Esto
okay and he answered it's normal for me to
vale y le ha respondido normal que
lower my head if I see a five foot pug
agache la cabeza si veo un pug de metro
walking on two
y medio andando a dos
legs I was already
patas
surprised that the best one was
ya me extrañaba a mí que el millor se
going to shut up
iba a callar
eh Javi but if you insult  to someone and
eh Javi pero si insultas a alguien y
then you can't even look at him if he's a
después ni lo puedes mirar si es un
little bit pathetic
poquito patético
[Music] let's
[Música]
see It depends on what insult and it depends on what you
e a ver Depende de qué insulto y depende
've
de qué es lo que hayas
said for me yes man if
dicho para mí si hombre si es insultado
someone is gratuitously insulted and you have
gratuitamente a alguien y le has dicho
only said insults not like for
solamente insultos no como por
example what example
ejemplo qué ejemplo
I give like for
pongo como por
example well this woman that we
ejemplo bueno la mujer esta que nosotros
have sued No, I don't know things are
hemos demandado No yo que sé las cosas
resolved in another way if someone
arreglan de otra forma si alguien te
insults you for me first of all it looks
insulta para mí en primer lugar queda
bad that the one who insults for free is
mal el que el que insulte gratuitamente
worth But if at a punctuated moment on the
vale Pero si en un momento puntuado en
internet you have heated up And both of you
internet os habéis calentado Y ambos
have said ugly things
habéis dicho cositas
one thing is an insult and another thing
feas una cosa es un insulto y otra cosa
is coming to blows I mean,
es llegar a las manos o sea yo es que el
coming to blows forgive me but I
llegar a las manos perdonadme pero lo
see it a little
veo un poco
uncivilized Well inhuman in fact I don't
incivilizado Bueno inhumano de hecho no
see it a little ape why would I
lo veo un poco de simio para qué os voy
deceive you if you tell me that there is
a engañar si tú me dices a mí que hay
someone who is doing something to your
alguien que le está haciendo algo a tu
sister and you have to go in and
hermana y te tienes que meter a a
beat the [ __ ] out of him obviously there I do see
cagarlo a porrazo evidentemente ahí sí
it let's
lo
see It's true that these
veo a ver también Es verdad que esta
people are of other ages then
gente tienen otras edades entonces a lo
maybe you see it more normal eh And maybe
mejor lo veis más normal eh Y a lo mejor
I already see it from the respective of my
yo ya lo veo desde la respectiva de mis
38 years okay Yes it's true that I
38 años vale Sí que es verdad que yo
saw the world differently when I
veía el mundo de otra manera cuando
was 20 20 something years old and yes maybe
tenía 20 20 y pico años y sí que a lo
things were resolved Well the thing is that I
mejor pues se solucionaban las cosas
was also more of a cane than the
Pues es que también era más can que la
host what am I going to tell you of course I mean
[__] qué os voy a decir claro o sea yo
when I saw that as normal well when I
cuándo lo veía eso normal pues cuando
was a chai from the neighborhood you know what I mean but
era un cani del barrio me entiendes pero
man to this day I see fights it's that I
hombre yo a día de hoy yo tema peleas es
see it as pathetic pathetic
veo
pathetic for me when the better one
patético para mí cuando el millor
insulted
insultó al
Comanche well in the first place it seems to me
Comanche bueno en primer lugar me suena
that the better one insulting Comanche
que lo del millor insultando a Comanche
happened after the evening that
fue después de la velada que vino
Comanche came here I didn't do the interview with him and I
Comanche aquí no le hice la entrevista y
think it was after the evening it doesn't
creo que es posterior a la velada no me
seem like it was before Okay and But
suena que fuera anterior Vale y Pero
well the better one didn't look bad for me
bueno no quedó mal el moror para mí
the better one
quedó mal el millor
And now what's your solution I mean what's
Y ahora cuál es tu solución O sea cuál
your answer that when you meet
es tu respuesta que cuando os encontráis
in person you
en persona echáis
look at each other and in case you
miradas y y en el caso de que tú me
hit me or I hit you what is it  it's
pegues o yo te pegue qué es lo que se
solved or rather what is it What is the what is
soluciona o sea cuál es Cuál es la cuál
the victory what is the answer to
es la victoria cuál es la respuesta a
that I don't know I find it a little
eso no sé lo veo un poco
pathetic I find it a little pathetic
patético lo veo un poco patético
the
la
truth is the millor made fun of him for the
verdad el millor se burló de él por la
evening and then for the video of
velada y después por el vídeo de la
Comanche's automation he made fun of him
automación de Comanche se burló de él
for the evening he made fun of Comanche before
por la velada se burló de Comanche antes
previously the
anteriormente el
millor let's see if you're an ape Well if
millor a ver si eres un simio Pues si
you can fix things like that Not with
puedes arreglar las cosas así No con
blows with looks and things like that but I'm
golpes con miradas y esas cosas no pero
telling you I mean I find it a little pathetic
ya te digo o sea lo veo un poco patético
eh I find it a little
eh lo veo un poco
pathetic I'm not going to tell you
patético no os voy a decir lo
otherwise for Seeking Ibai's attention
contrario por Buscar la atención de
Of course dude we saw it here
ibai Claro que sí churra lo vimos aquí
Oh yeah we saw it
Ah sí lo vimos
here I don't remember that I do
aquí no me acuerdo de
n't remember that let's
eso no me acuerdo de
see it's that we see so many things man
eso a ver es que vemos tantas cosas tío
that I only let's see if it's been a year Well
que solo me a ver si ha pasado un año
maybe I only remember
Pues a lo mejor solamente me acuerdo de
The gossip Strong and powerful don't notice
Los salseos Fuertes y potente no fijaros
that yesterday for example with the subject By the
que ayer por ejemplo con lo del tema Por
way have you seen the video that we
cierto habéis visto el vídeo que hemos
uploaded I uploaded a video with eh with
subido he subido un vídeo con eh con
Soul I uploaded a video here on this
Soul he subido un vídeo aquí en este
channel with Soul  in which we uncover
canal con Soul en el que destapamos
some little lie from yesterday about
alguna mentirilla de ayer del del
Luisito's
Luisito
communication let's see luares just sent me
comunic a ver me acaba de mandar luares
the response he gave wco to this
la respuesta que ha dado wco la esta
mess I tagged
movida yo he etiquetado a
Fran
Fran
on Twitter right now with the
en Twitter ahora mismo con la
photo No at all it's an attempt to
fotografía No para nada es un intento de
stir up a hornet's nest okay just like let's
mover el avispero vale simplemente como
see so you can give us an idea still a
a ver para que nos de idea tovías un
kiss handsome new pet how do we name it
beso guapo nueva mascota cómo le ponemos
westcol photo okay And he has
fotografía de westcol vale Y tiene aquí
a bird here that you're giving me the
un pájaro que me estáis poniendo el
name of the Bird there in the chat and
nombre del Pájaro por ahí por el chat y
apparently it's very common
por lo visto que es muy común
in some area of Latin America it's not
en en alguna zona de latinoamérica no es
what you're telling me no what you
lo que me estáis diciendo no lo que me
're telling me is that it's very common no
estáis diciendo es que es muy común no
that it's a common bird to
que es un pájaro habitual de
see but I don't know what bird it is but it looks like it could
ver pero no sé qué pájaro es pero tiene
eat the eggs a vulture this
pinta de comerse las hechas un buitre no
isn't it no what the hell is it going to be a what the
es esto nobre qué [__] va a ser un qué
hell is it going to be a vulture they just put
[__] va a ser un buitre acaban de poner
the name before there if you put it back I'll read you
el nombre antes por ahí si lo volvéis a
okay But how are you going to carry
poner os Leo vale Pero cómo vas a llevar
a bird with a leash and on top of that the
un pájaro con Correa y encima de la
way he's carrying it tied here I think you
forma que lo lleva aquí atado creo que
could even hurt it I mean I think
le puedes hacer incluso daño o sea creo
if he pulls it will choke
que si él tira se ahoga
eh I think if he pulls he'll drown eh what are
eh creo que si él tira se ahoga eh qué
people saying here
gente
well but on
bueno pero es que
top of that it's that on top of that The koogi uploads a
encima es que encima El koogi sube un
video
vídeo
samuro is a black sopilote scavenger bird
samuro es un pájaro carroñero sopilote
okay let's see look at the
negro vale a ver pues mira los medios de
media El Heraldo newspaper
comunicación diario El
wcol
wcol maltratador de
animal abuser let's see what he
animales a ver vamos a ver qué es lo que
has responded if Luar has
ha respondido si por aquí me la ha
put it to me here because apparently it has already come out
puesto luar porque al parecer ha salido
in the media
ya en los medios
Look there is a l country in Colombia there is a
Mira hay un l país en Colombia hay un
lp
lop
country but in the last hours the
país pero en las últimas horas el
streamer shared on his social networks
streamer compartió en sus redes sociales
a photo of a bird tied to a rope
una foto de un ave atada a una cabulla
mentioning a new pet how do we
mencionando nueva mascota como le
surely name it for this Luis Villa
ponemos seguramente por esto Luis Villa
since he is a real man he will have to be
como es un hombre real tendrá que ser
investigated And of course generating a
investigado Y por supuesto generando
hundred opinions on social networks wc
Cent de opiniones en redes sociales wc
animal abuser wc
maltratador de animales wc maltratador
animal abuser what a
animales qué
gem what a
joya qué
gem please yesterday I uploaded a photo come on come on you're going to say that let's
joya por favor ayer sub una foto venga
see to say
venga ya va decir que a veré a decir
gall amarr a photo that has been
gall amarr una foto que lleva dando
circulating on the internet for a long time and
vueltas por internet mucho tiempo y se
became a meme it turns out that today I
convirtió en un meme resulta que hoy me
wake up and I'm funado in the middle Ah  so it's
levanto y estoy funado por medio Ah o
a photograph that is not
sea que es una fotografía que no es
sh that is a photograph that is not
sh que es una fotografía que no es
him Okay then we delete twi no
él Vale entonces eliminamos twi no
guys let's see I don't find the meme funny I
chavales a ver no me hace gracia al meme
don't find the meme funny obviously
no me hace gracia al meme evidentemente
but I mean it's a photo that is already on the
pero o sea es una foto que ya está en
internet and he uploads it to his
internet y él la sube a sus historias de
Instagram stories as
Instagram como
his own let's see I don't find it funny but well
suya a ver gracia no la veo pero bueno
media outlets news and
medios de comunicación noticieros y
newspapers with explicit headlines that
periódicos con titulares explícitos que
say wescol is an
dicen wescol es un maltratador de
animal abuser daddy well And that is not even
animales papi bueno Y ese ya ni siquiera
the case anymore I'm used to
es el caso Yo ya estoy acostumbrado a
that but the message is the following they
eso pero el mensaje es el siguiente os
do that to you it's obvious those images are from the
hacen eso es obvio esas imágenes son de
Internet but but why was it obvious let's
Internet pero pero por qué era obvio a
see yo yo yo I see that from
ver yo yo yo eso lo veo de
wc and it doesn't
wc y a mí no me
surprise me let's see I'm not going to be
sorprende vamos a ver yo no me voy a
scared of something like that from
asustar de de una cosa así por parte de
wcol after the things we've
wcol después de las cositas que hemos
heard I mean it was obvious it was
escuchado o sea era evidente era
obvious Why Because you've seen the
evidente Por qué Porque habéis visto la
photo
foto
before actions and they want the
antes acciones y quieren las
interactions of those people haters
interacciones de esas personas haters
who spend their time watching things that don't
que se la pasan viendo cosas que ni
even nourish their mind daddy in this
siquiera le nutren la mente papi en este
country there are murders robberies and a lot of
país hay asesinatos robos y un montón de
things truly  serious enough for
cosas verdaderamente graves como para
people to spend time reading
que la gente le dedique tiempo a ver
those newspapers that spend their time telling
esos periódicos que se la pasan diciendo
lies simply to generate
mentiras simplemente para generar
interactions that's what
interacciones eso es lo que quieren
they want and thanks to that is why there are people
ellos y gracias a eso es que hay gente
so so but so
tan tan pero tan
brutal dude What a beauty that
bruta parce Qué belleza como quedó ese
dude turned out but I don't know which one to take out today although I'm
huevón pero no sé cuál sacar hoy aunque
going to sell some because I want to
alguno lo voy a vender porque quiero
buy one in Miami here I already have
comprarme uno en Miami aquí ya tengo
several Well but anyway It's that I don't
varios Bueno pero Igualmente Es que no
understand it was a meme But I don't understand
entiendo era un meme Pero no entiendo
What is the purpose of the Meme I mean
Cuál es el propósito del Meme o sea
it's simply a photo that has been on the
simplemente es una foto que que lleva en
internet for a while and the joke is like look look I have I have
internet tiempo y el chiste es como mira
a pet I don't have a
tengo tengo una mascota no tengo una
new pet well the
mascota nueva bueno el
humor the humor is that it escapes me that is
humor el humor a mí es que se me escapa
that humor the truth escapes me
esa es ese humor se me escapa la verdad
many times the humor of the
muchas veces el humor de
internet man with how much I like the
internet tío con lo que me gusta la
brand of the crocodile with how much I
marca del del cocodrilo con lo que me
like it eh How can he look so
gusta a mí eh Cómo se puede lucir tan
poo How can he look so little
poo Cómo se puede lucir tan poco
dude this What is it that they have already done the
tío esto Qué es que han hecho ya el
debate the dasas was going to do a debate with
debate el dasas iba a hac un debate con
him have they already done the debate or
él han hecho ya el debate o
what I mean how can he show off
qué O sea cómo se puede lucir
either oh my god no no the croc no the
tampoco ay madre mía no no la croc no la
crocs no let's see  Dalas has made a video
crocs no a ver Dalas ha hecho un vídeo
criticizing this man no What is a
criticando a este hombre no Qué es un
danif Flow you may have
danif Flow es posible que hayas
heard one Uf is that what this
escuchado una Uf es que lo que dijo este
man said was very strong eh what
hombre fue muy fuerte eh lo que dijo
this man said was very heavy
este hombre fue muy heavy
eh one of the most famous songs
eh una de las canciones más conocidas
that he has which is the reggaeton champan
que tiene que es la de reggaeton champan
Pam Pam p reggaeton
Pam Pam p regetón
champ true my ears hurt
champ verad me duelen los oídos
listening to it is absolutely deplorable I
escucharla es absolutamente deplorable
honestly thought that it was not a
pensaba Honestamente que no era una
song but simply a viral audio
canción sino simplemente un audio viral
of someone putting their voice through their
de alguien poniendo la voz a través del
cell phone on top of a crappy reggaeton base
móvil encima de una base de reggaetón
and people started to do it
cutre y la gente empezó a vir realizarla
on tiktok basically with this rhyme
por tiktok básicamente con esta rima de
here saying What beautiful eyes you have I
aquí diciendo Qué bonitos ojos tienes
want to suck your parakeet
Quiero chuparte el periquito
What beautiful eyes you have I want to suck your
Qué bonitos ojos tienes Quiero chuparte
penis with all due respect I hope it does not
el pene con todo respeto espero no te
bother you this was the rhyme that became
molest esta fue la rima que se hizo
popular I mean there are things that are not
popular Yo es que hay cosas que no
true I mean call me old eh I am
verdad O sea llamarme antiguo eh yo soy
your grandfather
vuestro abuelo
literally I mean
literalmente o sea
Listen listen to those lyrics those
Escuchar escuchar esas letras esas
songs having David Vival
canciones teniendo a David vival
having Jos Luis
teniendo a José Luis
Perales all over tiktok and mainly
Perales en todo tiktok y principalmente
thanks to that is what we are talking about let's
gracias a es lo que estamos hablando a
see as a song  meme no I mean like a
ver como canción meme no O sea como
meme song to be funny and
canción meme para para hacer la gracia y
to laugh for a while not about not to
para reírte un rato no de lo no para
put it as the background of a of a meme
ponerlo como de fondo de un de un meme
of a meme okay But as to
de un meme vale Pero como para
really listen to it in a non-
escucharla en realidad de manera no
ironic way imagine yourself in your car at
irónica imagínate en tu coche en el
that guy's gym because in the world
gimnasio de ese tío porque en el mundo
of no advertising is bad because this
de ninguna publicidad es mala pues este
Tom Thumb has gone viral And of
Pulgarcito se ha hecho viral Y por
course when it went viral people
supuesto la gente cuando la hecho viral
started checking to see what was
ha empezado a revisar a ver qué había
behind this guy The guy was dedicated
detrás de este señor El tío se dedicaba
to saying garbage fart T yes it's
a decir basuras pedo T sí le está
taking Dallas a while lower it lower the
tardando al Dallas bajala bajala
swelling eh without the slightest
hinchazón eh sin el menor
question about it but the thing is
cuestionamiento al respecto lo pero es
that a lot of people are defending him and
que mucha gente le está defendiendo y
saying oh quo a rhyme but as because
diciendo ay quo una rima pero as porque
this is not worth it You're welcome let's see this
esto no vale De nada vamos a ver esto
first the chile in 15 years of this rhyme
primero el chile en 15 años de esta rima
I'm going to regret it but I saw it from the
me voy a arrepentir pero la vi des de
moment if I have to live them I would
momento si los tengo que vivir a mi
never touch it for those
jamás la tocaría por esas compañeritas
high school classmates maybe yes to their
de la secundaria tal vez s sí a sus
Come on come on come on come on come on eh And
Vamos vamos vamos vamos vamos vamos eh Y
the guy told you like something deep
el tío te lo dijo como algo profundo
you know like look I'm going to be  Honestly, you
sabes como si mira voy a ser sincero
know, a lot of people are
sabes es que mucha gente le está
defending him and saying, oh, just a
defendiendo y diciendo ay que solo una
rhyme, but because this is worthless.
rima pero as porque esto no vale De nada
Let's see this first. In 15
vamos a ver esto primero el chile en 15
years of this rhyme, I'm going to regret it,
años de esta rima me voy a arrepentir
but I'll ask you for it. For now, if I have to
pero la pid des de momento si los tengo
live it, I would never play it for
que vivir a mi jamás la tocaría para
those high school classmates,
esas compañeritas de la secundaria tal
maybe yes, to
vez s sí a
their, and it's a rhyme, eh. It's that
sus y es una rima eh Yo es que eso de la
rhyme. I don't see the art in it, the
rima Yo es que no le veo el arte la
truth is that I don't like it. I
verdad es que a mí no me gusta Yo
respect it. Look, we have Quesada,
respeto Mira nosotros tenemos al Quesada
not Quesada, for example, I
no el Quesada por ejemplo a mí me cae
really like him,
muy bien
eh, and he really likes
eh y a él le gusta mucho lo del
freestyle. No, in fact. His content on
freestyle No de hecho Su contenido sobre
that, no, I don't understand that taste, I
eso no yo ese gusto no lo entiendo la
honestly don't understand. Where's the pleasure
verdad no entiendo Dónde está el gusto
in a guy telling you to make a rhyme
en que un tío para hacer una rima te
that something that surely
diga que una cosa que seguramente se le
goes through his head,
pasa por la cabeza
no, high school classmates, a
no compañeritas de la secundaria un
little context, in Mexico,
poquito de contexto en México la
high school is for 12 to 14 years old, here
secundaria es de 12 a 14 años aquí no
we're not even talking about pedophilia,
estamos siquiera hablando de pedofilia
pilia. I don't know how to pronounce it, I never
pilia no sé cómo se pronuncia nunca me
remember.  we're not talking about
acuerdo no no estamos hablando de
literally the guy talking about being a
literalmente el tío hablando de ser un
fart saying that his
pedo diciendo que las compañeras de la
daughter's high school classmates because the guy
secundaria de su hija porque el tío
has a
tiene una
daughter well this would be feb ophilia I
hija bueno esto sería de feb ofilia
understand also
entiendo también
equally no I don't know From what age would it be
igualmente no no sé A partir de qué edad
feb ophilia But well it's that I don't give a
sería feb ofilia Pero bueno es que me da
[ __ ] I mean how the [ __ ] are you going to
[__] igual o sea cómo [__] vas a
say that you would touch
decir que tocarías a niñas de la
high school girls I mean it's that I don't care what
secundaria o sea es que me da igual el
term we want to give it and the daughter
término que le queramos poner y la hija
has two mothers You're going to freak out with this
tiene dos madres Vais a flipar con esto
with two balls did this I know to say
con dos huevos hizo esto ya se a decir
that yesterday er Nobody until literally
que ay er Don nadie hasta literalmente
this last year he got into
este último año que se metía dentro de
these groups that meet in parks to
estos grupos que quedan en parques para
do freestyle they do the typical
hacer freestyle hacen las típicas
freestyle battles I have done I don't
batallas de freestyle yo que he hecho no
understand it much But well I respect
lo entiendo mucho Pero bueno Yo respeto
people's tastes it's like if
los gustos de la gente es como si
someone says that it gives them cringe that I
alguien dice que le da cringe que me
really like Disney movies
gusta a mí mucho las películas de Disney
no Well to me they seem like
no Bueno a mí me parecen
art there are people who find this
arte hay gente a la que le parece esto
art fun I don't know it's like when
arte diversión No lo sé es como cuando
Quesada do you remember Gabrielo a kiss
el Quesada os acordáis gabrielo un beso
handsome Thank you very much
guapo Muchas
What do you say Why haven't you written
gracias Qué dice Por qué no has escrito
anything David Vival has songs
nada David vival tiene canciones
talking  from suque AR nepes no let's see but
hablando de suque AR nepes no a ver pero
David Vival let's see that for
David vival vamos a ver es que eso para
me is art beautiful lyrics lyrics that
mí es arte letras bonitas letras que te
are telling you and that are speaking to you
estén diciendo y que te estén hablando
that are speaking to you about love that
que te estén hablando del amor que te
are speaking to you about sex even but in a
estén hablando del sexo incluso pero de
romantic way and he has told you with
manera romántica y te lo ha dicho con
a
una
profound phrase Look you'll see
frase profunda Mira verás
[Music]
[Música]
mm Jos Luis
mm José Luis
Peral a song Let's see which for
Peral una canción A ver cuál por
example my students asked me to
ejemplo mis alumnos me pidieron que
never listen to this song and with my
nunca escuchara esta canción y con mis
colleagues we listened to it at a meeting at
colegas la escuchamos en una reunión en
school and we were
la escuela y nos
scared man it's that it's very strong it's
espantamos hombre es que es muy fuerte
that justifying everything in it's a rhyme
es que justificar todo en es una rima
okay let's see and you go no And how is he And
vale a ver y tú te vas no Y cómo es él Y
how is he I mean here he's telling you about
cómo es él o sea aquí te está contando
an infidelity of his relative and he's
una infidelidad de la parienta y te lo
telling you in a
está contando de manera
romantic way I mean you're empathizing with the
romántica O sea estás empatizando con el
poor man who has felt the abandonment
pobre hombre que ha sentido el abandono
of a woman okay
de una mujer vale
mm slave to your kisses
mm esclavo de tus besos
man slave to your kisses and I'm still a slave
tío esclavo de tus besos y sigo esclavo
to your kisses where is she
de tus besos dónde está
Don't ask me why sometimes I
la No me preguntes por qué a veces la
name her by chance And it's that I still
nombro por casualidad Y es que aún la
remember her I am like this and I will continue wandering
recuerdo Yo soy así y seguiré vagando
errant through your skin I won't be able  give it
errante por tu piel Yo no podré dar todo
my all as long as I don't forget that woman
de mí mientras que no olvide a esa mujer
okay I mean he's telling you that his
vale o sea te está contando que tiene la
head is somewhere else Okay he's got it his
cabeza en otra papa Vale que tiene la la
head couldn't catch on and he can't focus with
cabeza no atrapaba y no se centra con
any new girl he's telling the
ninguna nueva chica se lo está contando
new girl okay we understand
a la nueva chica vale entendemos
no and You read this and this is art this is
no y Tú lees esto y esto es arte esto es
art 24 hours a day I also really like it
arte 24 horas también me gusta mucho
Look sorry if I can't find my
Mira perdón si no encuentro mi
emotional stability I regret if I
estabilidad emocional me arrepiento si
told you that I wasn't going to look for you anymore Sorry
te dije que ya no te iba a buscar Perdón
if I look for you and cry in your face sorry if I
si te busco y lloro en tu cara perdón si
ruined a date for you we took
una cita te la he echado a perder nos
some time and I'm still here waiting you
dimos un tiempo y sigo aquí esperando
said my boy I promise we'll get
dijiste mi niño te prometo que vamos a
back together kid you're a loser they screwed you
volver chaval eres un pagafantas te la
okay They screwed you
han dado con queso vale Te la han dado
When someone tells you Let's
con queso Cuando alguien te dice Vamos a
take some time I have to clear my
darnos un tiempo tengo que aclarar mi
mind she's going to be sleeping with half the
mente se va a estar tirando a medio
neighborhood and she's not going to come back to you unless
barrio y no va a volver contigo a no ser
life doesn't go well for her okay
que no le vaya bien la vida vale que no
the plan doesn't go well okay I mean how are you
le vaya bien el plan vale o sea cómo me
going to compare that to touch I wouldn't touch
vas a comparar eso con toca no tocaría a
my daughter but I would touch my friends [ __ ]
mi hija pero sí tocaría a las amigas
it's that if I  you're watching
hostias es que si me estáis viendo
anyone who has kids in
cualquiera que tengáis hijos en la
high school you'll understand the
secundaria estaréis entendiendo la
repugnance of this let's say the repugnance
repugnancia de esto vamos la repugnancia
is to not bring him near I mean to not
es para no acercarlo O sea para no
let him be seen on the perimeter of the
dejarlo ver en el perímetro del
institute picking up his daughter so they don't
instituto recogiendo a la hija para que
allow him to be in the area How are you
no le permitan estar por la zona Cómo
putting colors mino for God but
que pustos colores mino por Dios pero
this is like when Quesada
esto es como cuando el
wanted to refute me about that guy I
me quiso rebatir lo de que el tipo ese
don't remember what his name was that he was a
no me acuerdo cómo se llamaba que era un
guy who in the end threatened me do you remember
tío que al final me amenazó os acordáis
that I made a video commenting and the guy
que hice un vídeo comentando y el tío me
wanted to hit me He threatened to hit me
quería pegar Me amenazó con pegarme
then he came up we had a debate and he apologized I
luego subió hicimos un debate y me pidió
think it was I don't remember what his
perdón Creo que fue no me acuerdo cómo
name was one of these freestylers
se llamaba uno de estos del freestyler
no that apparently he said he charged
no que por lo visto decía él que cobraba
500 for
500 por
collaborations that he wanted to hit me or whatever
colaboraciones que me quería pegar o sea
Ah yeah V A little bit of the civility not of the
Ah ya V Un poco la el civismo no de la
people and the one who didn't want to justify to me that that what
gente y el que nada me quería justificar
the guy said in a
que que que lo que dijo el tío en una
rhyme that Dallas was a pedophile
rima de que el Dallas era un pedófilo
well it was a rhyme it wasn't literal you know
pues era una rima no era literal sabes
how that I this let's see what the [ __ ] you're
cómo que yo esto a ver qué [__] me estás
telling me that  not like you but to me
contando que no sea vosotros pero a mí
personally it seems that 99.9% of
personalmente se me hace que el 99,9 de
these people make the
estas personas hacen todo el rato las
same cheap rhymes all the time and it gives me a
mismas rimas baratas y me da auténtico
real cringe every time I listen to them
cring de verdad cada vez que les escucho
I say God I feel a pain here in my
digo Dios siento un dolor aquí en el
chest every time I hear them try to
pecho cada vez que les oigo intentar
make new rhymes and change the
hacer rimas nuevas y cambiar la
accentuation of the words I just can't
acentuación de las palabras es que no lo
stand it in the Spanish language it changes
soporto en el lenguaje español cambia
a lot to say this one that is And these little
mucho decir esta que está Y estos
rappers constantly modify the
raperillos constantemente modifican la
accentuation of the words Yes that is
acentuación de las palabras Sí eso se
done that is done words that they have said it's
hace eso se hace palabras que han dicho
like if it doesn't fit you that is done eh I
es como si no te cuadra eso se hace eh o
mean if it doesn't fit you if it doesn't fit you
sea si no te cuadra la si no te cuadra
the word you put it inside and [ __ ] it it
la la palabra la metes dentro y a tomas
works for me unbearable it gives me OCD I
por culo me sirve insoportable me da Toc
really feel cringe every time I
de verdad siento crin cada vez que los
listen to them I think 0.1 percent of the times
escucho creo que un 0,1 por de las veces
that I have seen some of these little
que he visto algun vez de estos
rappers do their freestyles I have not
raperillos hacer sus freestyles no he
felt a true cringe listening to them
sentido verdadero cringe escuchándoles
Because also in all the
Porque además siempre en todas las
battles they do they always use and repeat the
batallas que hacen usan y repiten las
same rhymes over and over again and they almost
mismas rimas una y otra vez y casi
always talk about how they are going to
siempre hablan sobre que se van a
benefit  to your mother 99% of the
beneficiar a tu madre el 99% de las
time at the time when it was
veces en la época en la que estaba de
fashionable to tell me any nonsense
moda decirme cualquier barbaridad
some of these yeah insults I don't know what
algunos de estos sí insultos no sé qué
bor a kiss little garbage dogs infected they
bor un beso perillos basura infectos se
dedicated themselves to doing these
dedicaban a hacer estas batallas de
rhyme battles literally mentioning me you're
rimas literalmente mencionándome eres
like a piece of [ __ ] if you're on
como pedazo de molo si techas de
Twitter all How embarrassing Well
Twitter todos Cuánta vergüenza Bueno
look but that one at least not but yes it is true it is
mira pero esa por lo menos no pero sí
true
que es verdad es verdad le dedicaban
many dedicated it to Dallas I have heard like that eh
muchos al Dallas yo he escuchado así eh
Not only the one with this guy who
No solamente la del chico este que le
called him a pedophile eh there was like that eh there were a
dijo pedófilo eh había así eh había unos
few Why doesn't dasas talk about
cuantos Por qué dasas no habla de
Comanche it's going to be a video it's going to be a
Comanche va a ser un vídeo va a ser un
video maybe I'll loose a little bit of the tongue
vídeo a lo mejor me un poco de la lengua
but as far as I know it was going to be a video as far as
pero que yo sepa iba a ser un vídeo que
I know it was going to be a video Well I think that
yo sepa iba a ser un vídeo Bueno yo creo
I think he recorded it many
que yo creo que lo grabó ya hace muchos
days ago the editor or whatever it is that
días lo subirá el editor o lo que sea
is fashionable will upload it to tell me any
que está de moda decirme cualquier
nonsense some of these little
barbaridad algunos de estos raperillos
garbage rappers infected they dedicated themselves to doing
basura infectos se dedicaron a hacer
these rhyme battles literally
estas batallas de rimas literalmente
mentioning me you're like a piece of [ __ ]
mencionándome eres como pedazo de molo
if you're on Twitter you're doing him a favor
si techas de Twitter le haces un favor a
all Well that one can still happen
todos Bueno esa esa todavía puede pasar
to me they tell me that and I laugh even okay
a mí me dicen esa y me río incluso vale
But there was the usual thing was to call him a
Pero había lo habitual era decirle
pedophile abuser and those things the
pedófilo maltratador y esas cosas la
rhyme is that it is that it is a battle it is
rima ya es que es que es una batalla es
how embarrassing you can be and how
cómo vergüenza ajena puedes dar y como
cowardly you have to be to throw yourself at
de cobarde tienes que ser para tirarle a
someone you are not even
alguien con ni siquiera te estás
fighting only to win the
peleando únicamente para ganarte el
applause of the public we fly to the dan Flow
aplauso del público volamos al dan Flow
is the only one who talks about garbage in his songs it
es el único que habl en sus canciones
is I want you to get on all fours so you do
basura es quiero que te pongas en cuatro
n't get a fever so you can
que no te dé fiebre para que tú me lo
bury it for me they only talk about bronj about
entierres solo hablan de bronj de
maintaining adult relationships or
mantener relaciones para adultos o de
both at the same time great
las dos cosas al mismo tiempo grandes
rhymes from the Spanish ark Like for
rimas de la arca española Como por
example I'm going to glacier the donut
ejemplo te voy a glaciar la dona
basically the icing sugar is white what you have
básicamente el azúcar glass es blanco lo
between your buttocks is in this
que tienes entre las nalgas es en este
case the donut and what's going to put
caso el donut y que le va a poner azúcar
icing sugar on it Well I think it's obvious what he's
glass Pues creo que es evidente lo que
going to do with your Gift the quietest ones
va a hacer con tu Don las más calladitas
are the most [ __ ] ahem ahem ons You
son las más put ejem ejem onas Te
love ver ahem you're going to [ __ ]
encanta la ver ejem vas a [__] para
inside anyway look at the [ __ ] lyrics You
dentro sea que tú mira la [__] letra Me
're comparing me this with this I mean
estáis comparando esto con esto O sea
look at you eh You're
fíjate tú
going to [ __ ] yourself I'm going to
eh Te vas a [__] para dentro te voy a
put sugar on the
poner azúcar en el
donut feel the power of the
donut siente el power del
bogetto don't [ __ ] with me don't [ __ ] with me are you going to
bogetto no me jodas no me jodas me vas a
compare that
comparar eso
with Look at this my God look at
con Mira esta por Dios mira
this a lot of people say that men
esta dice mucha gente que los hombres
never cry but I had to go
nunca lloran pero yo he tenido que
back to my childhood once again I keep
volver a mi niñez una vez más me sigo
asking myself why I keep loving you and you
preguntando por qué te sigo amando y
left my wounds bleeding man my
dejaste sangrando mis heridas hombre por
God if I'm going to fall in love and I'm
Dios si es que me voy a enamorar yo y le
going to eat the mouth of the one who wrote
voy a comer la boca yo al que ha escrito
this but don't [ __ ] with me man what are we we
esto per no me jodáis tío que estamos
are turning art into pure
estamos convirtiendo el arte en pura
diarrhea damn don't
diarrea [__] no me
[ __ ] with me while I get in and I p etro you and
jodas mientras lo entro y te p etro y
everything I'm seeing a guy who looks like
todo estoy viendo un tipo que parece un
Kim Jong un with a midlife crisis who
Kim Jong un con la crisis de los 50 que
also put his own nickname on his
además se puso su propio Mote en la
chin that this man doesn't have one
barbilla que este señor no tiene una
girlfriend he doesn't have two and you'll say what and I'm
novia no tiene dos y dirás qué y yo te
telling you The young man of only 25 years old imprisoned
digo El joven de tan solo 25 años preso
spoiler is not 25 years old managed to get
spoiler no tiene 25 años conseguido que
Google to put that he is 21 years old which
en Google ponga que tiene 21 años cosa
is a lie the guy apparently is
que es mentira el tío al parecer tiene
28 years old man of almost 30 years old  saying
28 años señor de casi 30 añazos diciendo
and laughing at rhymes that he would like to
y riéndose de rimas de que le gustaría
touch girls between 12 and 14 his girlfriend
tocar a niñas de entre 12 y 14 su novia
and his wife Thanking Ah that he takes
y su esposa Agradeciendo Ah que se quita
years off for his love and I don't know if I'm
años por su amor y ya no sé si me
more worried about the fact that this guy
preocupa más el hecho de que este tipo
with the looks that takes me with the little
con las pintas que me lleva con la poca
brain cell he has has two girlfriends or if
neurona que tenga tiene dos novias o si
I'm more worried about the other one in the audience
me preocupa más la otra del público
screaming I love you to break her
gritando te amo para romperse las
vocal cords talking about this man
cuerdas vocales hablando de este señor
here by the way this one here is the
de aquí por cierto esta aquí es la
wife and this one here is the girlfriend and
esposa y esta de aquí es la novia y
look how he's holding the hand of the
fijaos como le está dando la mano a la
girlfriend and the wife like yes I'm
novia y la esposa en plan de sí estoy
being a sister Ha How funny Well but
siendo cuada Ja Qué divertido Bueno pero
you'll see in that sense if they
eso verás tú en ese sentido si están de
agree polyamorous relationships
acuerdo relaciones poliamorosas a mí
I really don't see it as bad Let's see I don't
realmente yo no lo veo mal A ver no
fully
termino de
understand it because Of course if you're
entenderlo porque Claro si tú estás
looking for
buscando
that Let's see it's another way of seeing life it's
eso A ver es otra forma de ver la vida
not bad eh he he's doing great He
no está mal eh é é él está de [__] madre
's enjoying himself because he has the one who
Está disfrutando porque tiene a la que
is his partner not his love not his wife
es su su pareja no su amor no su mujer
but then maybe he has another one
pero luego a lo mejor pues tiene a otra
that he also likes let's see you
que que también le gusta a ver a ti te
can like physically a lot of people and
puede gustar físicamente mucha gente y
you  can sexually attract a lot of people
te puede atraer sexualmente mucha gente
Even if you're in love I mean don't
Aunque tú estés enamorado O sea no me
[ __ ] with me okay but you'll see if you're
jodas vale pero verás tú si tú estás
satisfied and all No because it's that you know
satisfecho y tal No porque es que sabéis
what, surely seeing a little of the
qué que seguramente viendo un poco el
guy's profile he's really great
perfil del tío a él está de [__] madre
he thinks polyamory is great of having
le parece muy bien el poliamor de tener
a wife and a girlfriend but
una mujer y una novia pero
surely he wouldn't stand and wouldn't
seguramente no soportaría y no
allow the wife to have a
permitiría que la mujer tuviera un
boyfriend okay But well in this it doesn't matter it does
novio vale Pero bueno en esto da igual
n't hurt anyone with this if they
no hace daño a nadie con esto si ellos
agree to do it I understand that it does
están de acuerdo en hacerlo entiendo que
n't hurt anyone okay Javi polyamory
no hace daño a nadie vale Javi poliamor
with Loren and Paulo Echevarra sure let's see
con Loren y Paulo Echevarría claro a ver
but
pero evidentemente
obviously obviously the fact that you're
evidentemente el hecho de que tú estés
in love doesn't mean that you don't feel let's
enamorado no te hace que no sientas a
see a super attractive person can come to you
ver te puede venir una persona super
or who is very powerful and that
atractiva o que esté muy potente y que a
you like and yes if you were single
ti te guste y que si si fueras soltero
you know if you were
sabes si fueras
single okay but of course you don't do it
soltero vale pero claro no lo haces
because you have loyalty fidelity and all that
porque tienes lealtad fidelidad y demás
to your partner no more than anything because of
a tu pareja no más que nada por por
feelings okay to respect the
sentimientos vale por respetar los
feelings of the other person that's what
sentimientos de la otra persona es de lo
loyalty is about
que trata la lealtad
but if you agree it's not
pero si estás de acuerdo no es
incompatible it's not incompatible to love
incompatible no es incompatible querer a
your wife and have your life with your wife
tu mujer y tener tu vida con tu mujer
with being attracted to them  sexually other
con que te atraigan sexualmente otras
people so for me within what
personas entonces para mí dentro de lo
we are criticizing this man
que estamos criticando de este hombre
well this doesn't matter to me the truth is it is the
pues esto no me importa la verdad es lo
least and thank you very much for coming into
mínimo y muchas gracias por llegar a
our lives notice how he doesn't stop all the
nuestra vida fijaos có no para todo el
time touching the new one while the
rato de toquetear a la nueva mientras la
wife who by the way is the mother of his
esposa que por cierto es la madre de su
daughter How funny darling when in the middle
hija Qué divertido cariño cuánd en medio
of thousands of people How funny
de miles de personas Qué divertido
darling cuame more please Of course but
cariño cuame más por favor Claro pero es
for me it wouldn't be
que para m no sería
if it's something that you
si es una cosa con la que estás de
agree with it's not cuqueo no cuqueo it's when
acuerdo no es cuqueo no cuqueo es cuando
you
tú
are you are a Cook when
eres tú eres un Cook cuando
you swallow everything without you
tú tragas por todo sin tú querer en
really wanting to but you swallow
realidad pero tragas
because or so for example I don't
porque o sea por ejemplo Es que no
want to give you an example of a Cook
quiero poneros un ejemplo de un Cook
right now not because I don't want to start
ahora mismo no porque no quiero levantar
a battle here no but for
yo aquí una batalla no pero yo por
example there are two youtubers well some
ejemplo hay dos youtubers bueno unos
streamers that for me are
streamers que para mí son
cc
cc
okay in what sense well one of them
vale en qué sentido pues uno de ellos
for
por
example
ejemplo permite
allows any base on the part
ser permite cualquier basile por parte
of the relative and that the relative
de la parienta y que la parienta
[Music]
[Música]
m that I don't want to get into trouble let's see
m que no me quiero meterse fregado a ver
Yes well that the relative eh have it that
Sí bueno que la parienta eh lo tenga que
the relative have it there eh I don't know
la parienta lo tenga ahí eh yo que sé
why but without  However, the relative
por qué pero sin embargo la parienta
Well, don't mind exposing yourself or or I
Pues no le importe exponerse o o yo que
know the truth, I don't know why I'm
sé la verdad no sé por qué estoy
saying that and then there's another Cook for
opinando eso y luego hay otro Cook para
me who is another type of cuqueo who is a
mí que es otro tipo de cuqueo que es una
person who
persona que
does everything, I mean for me he's a
hace todo o sea para mí es una
person who doesn't completely satisfy his partner
persona que a su pareja no le llena del
but is using him
todo sino que lo está utilizando
Simply because because he
Simplemente porque por por porque lo
can disaro because he can get something out of
puede disaro porque puede sacar algún de
him, no
él no
and he orders him and orders him to be and he like a
e y le manda y le manda a ser y él como
good Cook, well, he does everything that he's
buen Cook pues hace todo lo que le
ordered to do, I don't know I mean, I'm not going to get
manden yo que sé O sea no me voy a meter
into that mess, everyone does what they do
en ese fregado cada uno allá lo que hace
in their
en sus
relationships and he gets involved and tries to give her
relaciones y se mano y le intenta dar
a hand What are we seeing, his daughter would
una alada Qué estamos viendo a su hija
never touch her, it's like why
jamás la tocaría que es como por qué
exactly are you making that excuse of
exactamente estás haciendo esa excusa de
an accusation that nobody made you, he's at
una acusación que nadie te hizo está en
a concert with his daughter in his arms and
un concierto con su hija en brazos y
let's see what he's going to do, he also
vamos a ver lo que va a hacer también
says for women Wait, he's the
dice para las mujeres Espérate que es
biggest feminist in the world, he made this
más feminista del mundo que hizo esta
song for
canción para las
women, he has his daughter in his arms
mujeres tiene a su hija en brazos
while he's talking about the
mientras está hablando de la parte de
back of women and that apparently is
atrás de las mujeres y eso al parecer es
perfect content to have his
un contenido perfecto para tener a su
daughter  In this concert talking
hija Dentro de este concierto hablando
about nonsense and filth of course
de barbaridades Y guarradas claro que sí
the tattoo he has here in Chinese on his
el tatuaje que tiene aquí en chino en la
cheek Google Translate literally
mejilla literalmente Google Translate lo
translates it as McDonald's and I'm not from c
traduce como McDonald's y no estoy de c
chile in 15 years of this rhyme I'm going to
chile en 15 años de esta rima me voy a
regret it but life is about moments and I
arrepentir pero la vida es de momento y
have to live them life is about
los tengo que vivir la vida es de
moments and I have to live them I would never
momentos y los tengo que vivir jamás la
touch it for those
tocaría por esas compañeritas de la
high school classmates maybe yes doing
secundaria tal vez s sí haciendo
Freestyle nobody forces you to say the
Freestyle nadie te obliga a qué decir la
people who say oh he doesn't
gente que dice ay esto no lo piensa él
really think this because he's just opening
realmente porque solo Está abriendo
freestyle Look dude there are a ton of
freestyle Mira colega hay un montonazo
thousands of rappers who are dedicated to
miles de raperillos que se dedican a
doing freestyle none of them have to
hacer freestyle ninguno de ellos tiene
at any time if they don't want to
por qu en ningún momento si no quiere
make a rhyme being a fart at any
hacer una rima siendo un pedo en ningún
time maybe we could say and it would be
momento tal vez podríamos decir y sería
the only salvageable part of this is that he
la única parte salvable de esto que él
had made this rhyme and didn't really
hubiese hecho esta rima y en realidad no
say what he thought let's imagine for
dijera lo que pensaba imaginemos por
example an actor acting like a fart
ejemplo a un actor actuando ser un pedo
but it's an act in this case he
pero es una actuación en este caso él no
wasn't acting at all he said
estaba actuando absolutamente nada dijo
that Because he really wanted to and he said it
eso Porque le dio la real gana y lo dijo
Why Well because he thinks about it there are a
Por qué Pues porque lo piensa hay una
lot of men  really overwhelming
cantidad de hombres realmente abrumante
repulsive and I've talked about some of
repulsiva y he hablado de algunos de
them here on the channel who are men
ellos aquí en el canal que son hombres
with tendencies to be farts Like for
con tendencias de ser pedos Como por
example Town Gameplays one of the
ejemplo Town Gameplays uno de los cados
most well-known cados here on the Town Channel
más conocidos de aquí del Canal he Town
What a good Tula who had relations
Qué buena Tula que mantuvo relaciones
with a 13 year old girl in a movie theater and there is
con una chica de 13 en unos cines y hay
evidence of this everywhere is that he
pruebas de esto por todos sitios es que
looks for girls between 12 and 14 years old that
busca chicas de entre 12 y 14 años que
he himself considers that maybe it would be up
él mismo se plantee que tal vez sí le
to the high school girls in
tocaría a las chicas de secundaria en
Mexico who are between 12 and 14 Oh but it
México que tienen entre 12 y 14 Ay pero
's humor it was all for laughs I would like
es humor era todo de risas me gustaría
someone to come here explain to me What
que alguien vene aquí me explicara Cuál
's the joke because I have to laugh that
es el chiste porque me tengo que reír de
this guy says that he would like to
que este tipo diga que le gustaría
glacier the donut to a girl between 12
glaciar la dona a una chica de entre 12
and 14 Where's the funny thing that this guy
y 14 Dónde está la gracia que este tipo
is collaborating Recently with jery mua
está colaborando Hace poco con jery mua
I'm just a brati puti in Colombia
Yo solo soy una brati puti en Colombia
stop labeling me and attacking me for
dejen de etiquetarme y atacarme por
[ __ ] that the unga unga say what the
[__] que dicen los unga unga qué los
unga unga but yes Those who were
unga unga pero si Quienes más le estaban
denouncing him the most are precisely the
funando a él son precisamente las
feminists not the unga unga yes  go H
feministas no los unga unga si ve H de
that I missed a kiss elison
que me he perdido un beso elison
Sincere apology for the
Disculpa sincera ante las declaraciones
literal statements against women but
en contra literal hacia la mujer pero
what is this lady saying? Have you
qué dice esta señora se ha enterado
even understood what this joke is about? So many
siquiera de qué va esta funa tantos
porra acos have left her with two
porra acos le han dejado con dos
exact neurons the question here is
neuronas justas la pregunta aquí es por
why are they joking around with me? Let me see if I can explain it to you
qué me funan a mí déjame ver que te lo
Jeri. First of all, nobody was
explico jeri primero nadie la estaba
joking with Jeri at any time. What I
funando a jeri en ningún momento lo que
saw most was people asking her how she could
más vi es gente preguntándole cómo podía
collaborate with this man and her
colaborar con este señor y a su
response, in her usual narcissism of
respuesta en su narcisismo de siempre de
all her life, was as always to play the
toda la vida fue como siempre hacersela
victim because that is the only card she
víctima porque es la única carta que
knows how to play and what she also did was to
sabe sacar y lo que hizo además fue
pave the way like, Oh, a sincere
allanar ya el terreno en plan de Ay una
apology. How is it that a
disculpa sincera Cómo que una disculpa
sincere apology? Do you really believe that a
sincera Tú te crees de verdad que una
person who is capable of saying such
persona que es capaz de decir esas
barbarities and who for many
barbaridades y que has durante un montón
years has laughed at having said that,
de años riéndose de haber dicho eso
now an apology from him is worth
ahora una disculpa de él vale de
absolutely nothing, he is still the same
absolutamente nada sigue siendo la misma
garbage person, an apology is not an
basura de persona una disculpa no es un
Oh you know what, I have realized that the
Ay sabes qué me he dado cuenta que las
things I said were wrong, no no, what he has
cosas que dije estuvieron mal no no lo
done, now you will see, is
que ha hecho que ahora lo veréis es
first to dedicate himself  to laugh about the subject and
primero dedicarse a reírse del tema y
then pretend that Ah they take everything out of
después a fingir que Ah lo sacan todo de
context obviously he really wanted
contexto obviamente tenía muchas ganas
to join the place that is hottest
de sumarse al lugar que más calienta que
at this moment because this guy well
en este momento pues este tipo pues
had quite a bit of fame and he said oh an
tenía bastante famita pues y dijo ay una
apology and that's it because she wanted to
disculpa y ya está porque ella quería
benefit from the numbers of the other
beneficiarse de los números del otro
to continue raising her failed musical career
para seguir subiendo su carrera musical
Now yes Leave me alone do not
fallida Ahora sí Déjenme en paz no me
involve me in disgusting controversies that I
metan en polémicas asquerosas que no
have nothing to do tip does not talk about that
tengo nada que ver tip no habla de que
the guy is a jerk but rather talks about
el tipo es un pedo sino que habla de que
statements against women
declaraciones en contra hacia la mujer
Here the problem is her
Aquí el problema son sus impulsos de
jerk impulses those are the ones who go out to scratch their
pedo esas es las que salen a rayar sus
[ __ ] in the street those two those
pendejadas en la calle las dos esas esas
not even rucas should call or I mean it is
no ni rucas deberían de llamar o sea es
and Total what happened have they already done the
y Total qué ha pasado han hecho ya el
debate they have not done the debate yet let's
debate no han hecho el debate todavía a
see Dallas put it like it was going to be a
ver el Dallas puso como que iba a ser un
debate with him this guy left him a
debate con él este tipo le le dejó un
comment on the
comentario en el
video but they did not report me for
vídeo pero a mí no me denunciaron por
sexual abuse okay I mean yes I have said that
sexual vale o sea sí yo he dicho que me
I have said that I would touch
yo he dicho que tocaría a las amigas de
my daughter's friends But well at least they did not
mi hija Pero bueno por lo menos a mí no
report me for sexual abuse and then it
me denunciaron por abuso sexual ya luego
gives  maybe it were true Or if it were a
da igual si fuera verdad O si fuera
lie okay But they didn't report me
mentira vale Pero a mí no me denunciaron
and the nonsense I don't know if he posted
y las movidas no sé si me ha puesto aquí
the tweet here Oh he didn't post it The thing
el twit Ay no me lo ha puesto La Movida
is that today Dallas posted a tweet eh
Es que hoy el Dallas puso un tweet eh
stating that he had a date with Danny
afirmando que había quedado con Danny
Flow to do a live today and if they haven't
Flow para hac hoy un directo y si no la
done it yet I understand that the live has been
han hecho ya entiendo que ese directo se
canceled because he said he was going to
ha cancelado porque dijo que lo iba a
do it on the main channel and also with
hacer en el canal principal además con
a
un
debate So I understand
debate Así que entiendo
[Music]
[Música]
that it has been
que que se ha
canceled it has been
cancelado se ha
canceled or the guy must have chickened out or
cancelado o el tío se habrá rajado o lo
whatever and well what's going on with Quesada Quesada
sea y bueno qué pasa con Quesada Quesada
responds to Dallas about the freestyler
responde a Dallas sobre el freestyler
well let's see
bueno a ver
[Music]
[Música]
eh I don't know if I should rewind
eh No sé si poneros un poco rebobinar
the live a little bit to
atrás un poco el directo para volver a
give you my opinion again on this
daros mi mi opinión sobre sobre el
freestyle that we were
freestyle este no que estábamos
[Music]
[Música]
talking about More than anything so as not
hablando Más que nada para no repetir
to repeat the same thing again no more than anything so as not to repeat the same thing again where have I commented on it here not about the familiar school and no I won't be able to give seeing anyone that you have children in
hijos en la
high school
secundaria
B  the head to see if it's taking
B la cabeza a ver si le está tardando
the high school classmates a
ales compañeritas de la secundaria un
little bit, well, it's that I don't care what
poquito sea es que me da igual el
term we want to give it, there are people who
término que le queramos poner hay gente
find this art fun I
a la que le parece esto arte diversión
don't know Here it is, let's see, it's like when
No lo sé Aquí está a ver es como cuando
the queada do you remember Gabriel A kiss
el queada os acordáis Gabriel Un beso
handsome
guapo Muchas
Thank you very much What does it say Why haven't you written
gracias Qué dice Por qué no has escrito
anything David bval has songs talking
nada David bval tiene canciones hablando
about suar nepes no let's see but David vival
de suar nepes no a ver pero David vival
let's see, that for me is art
vamos a ver es que eso para mí es arte
beautiful lyrics that are
letras bonitas letras que te estén
telling you and that are talking to you that
diciendo y que te estén hablando que te
are talking to you about love that are
estén hablando del amor que te estén
talking to you about sex even but in a
hablando del sexo incluso pero de manera
romantic way and he told you with a
romántica y te lo ha dicho con una
profound phrase Look, you'll see
frase profunda Mira verás
[Music]
[Música]
mm Jos Luis
mm José Luis
Peral a song Let's see which one, for
Peral una canción A ver cuál por
example, my students asked me to
ejemplo mis alumnos me pidieron que
never listen to this song and with my
nunca escuchara esta canción y con mis
colleagues we listened to it at a meeting at
colegas la escuchamos en una reunión en
school and we were
la escuela y nos
scared, man, it's very strong, it's
espantamos hombre es que es muy fuerte
that justifying everything in it's a rhyme
es que justificar todo en es una rima
okay let's see and you go no And how is he And how is he I
vale a ver y tú te vas no Y cómo es él Y
mean, here he is telling you about
cómo es él o sea aquí te está contando
an infidelity of his wife and he
una infidelidad de la parienta y te lo
is telling you in a way
está contando de manera
romantic I mean you're empathizing with the
romántica O sea estás empatizando con el
poor man who has felt abandoned
pobre hombre que ha sentido el abandono
by a woman okay
de una mujer vale
mm slave to your kisses
mm esclavo de tus besos
dude giving it my all as long as I don't
tío dar todo de mí mientras que no
forget that woman okay I mean he's
olvide a esa mujer vale o sea te está
telling you that he's got his head in another
contando que tiene la cabeza en otra
potato Okay he's got his head in another
papa Vale que tiene la cabeza en otra
potato and he's not focused with any new
papa y no se centra con ninguna nueva
girl he's telling the new
chica se lo está contando a la nueva
girl okay we understand
chica vale entendemos
no and You read fact and this is art this
no y Tú lees hecho y esto es arte esto
is
es
art 24 hours I also really like it
arte 24 horas también me gusta mucho
Look sorry if I can't find my
Mira perdón si no encuentro mi
emotional stability I regret if I
estabilidad emocional me arrepiento si
told you that we no longer team up with dan Flow is
te dije que ya no teamos al dan Flow es
the only one who talks in his songs trash it's I
el único que habl en sus canciones basur
want you to get on all fours so you don't get a
es quiero que te pongas en cuatro que no
fever so you can bury it for me they
te de fiebre para que tú me lo entierres
only talk about druggies maintaining ions
solo hablan de dronas de mantener iones
for adults or both at the same
para adultos o de las dos cosas al mismo
time great rhymes from Spanish arica
tiempo grandes rimas de arica española
Like for example I'm going to glacier the
Como por ejemplo te voy a glaciar la
donut basically powdered sugar is
dona básicamente el azúcar glass es
white what you have between your buttocks is
blanco lo que tienes entre las nalgas es
in this case the donut and what's going to
en este caso el donut y que le va a
put powdered sugar on it Well I think it's
poner azúcar glass Pues creo que es
obvious what he's going to do with your Gift
evidente lo que va a hacer con tu Don
the quietest are the  more [ __ ]
las más calladitas son las más putem
onas You love the verem you're going to [ __ ]
onas Te encanta las verem vas a [__]
inside you look at the [ __ ] lyrics You
para dentro tú mira la [__] letra Me
're comparing me to this I mean
estáis comparando esto con esto O sea
look at you eh You're going to [ __ ] inside I'm
fíjate tú eh Te vas a [__] para dentro
going to put sugar on the
te voy a poner azúcar en el
donut feel the power of the
donut siente el power del
bogetto
bogetto
don't [ __ ] with me don't [ __ ] with me you're going to
no me jodas no me jodas me vas a
compare that with Look at this my God look at
comparar eso con Mira esta por Dios mira
this a lot of people say that men
esta dice mucha gente que los hombres
never cry but I had to go
nunca lloran pero yo he tenido que
back to my children once again I keep
volver a mi niñes una vez más me sigo
asking myself why I keep loving you and you
preguntando por qué te sigo amando y
left my wounds bleeding man my
dejaste sangrando mis heridas hombre por
God if I'm going to fall in love I'm
Dios si es que me voy a enamorar yo le
going to eat the mouth of the one who wrote
voy a comer la boca yo al que ha escrito
this don't [ __ ] with me man what are we doing we're
esto no me joda tío que estamos estamos
turning art into pure
convirtiendo el arte en pura
diarrhea [ __ ] don't
diarrea [__] no me
[ __ ] with me Well I wanted I wanted to not have to
jodas Bueno quería quería no volver a
repeat my opinion
tener que que repetir mi opinión sobre
about freestyle no
sobre el freestyle no
this But anyway let's see what
este Pero bueno vamos a ver qué ha dicho
Quesada said about the Dallas video I
Quesada sobre el vídeo de Dallas yo
can get folter if he doesn't give me
puedo contrar folter como no me regale
10 subs I'll eat it for dessert on top of that I
10 sub me lo como de postre encima le
'm going to take off his bra if he raps he won't
voy a quitar el sostén si rapea no me
even make it to the top 10 I am the  typical that
llega ni al top 10 Yo soy el típico que
falls in the top three these [ __ ]
cae en el top tres estos hijos de [__]
better way
mejor camino
opt rapping like tote I'm praying like
opten rapeo like tote estoy rezando like
totem another astral plane my brother and that I
totem otro plano astral mi hermano y eso
'm not ilian astral I came to shoot
que no soy ilian astral yo vine a tirar
the basket Ah back I'm putting in
de la canasta Ah atrás estoy metiendo de
three without looking to basket There's Dani
tres sin mirar en cestar Ahí está Dani
Flow another of the things that annoys me danif
Flow otra de las cosas que me raya danif
Flow are his tattoos on his face
Flow son sus tatuajes en la cara
eh well anyway
eh bueno en
Quesada I love you very much and I like you very much
Quesada yo te quiero mucho y me caes muy
but he couldn't be more disgraced Yes with
pero no se podía desgraciar más Sí con
the tattoos Flow parks to do
los tatuajes Flow parques para hacer
freestyle they do the typical
freestyle hacen las típicas batallas de
freestyle battles that be careful eh I don't know about
freestyle que cuidado eh No sé a
you but to me personally it
vosotros pero a mí personalmente se me
seems that 99.9% of these people
hace que el 99,9 por de estas personas
do the same cheap rhymes all the time
hacen todo el rato las mismas rimas
and it gives me a real cringe
baratas y me da auténtico cringe de
really we have started very badly eh we have
verdad hemos empezado muy mal eh hemos
started very badly eh
empezado muy mal eh se le cayeron la
several cones fell through the sale to make some
venta varios conos para hacer unos
pretty strong comments regarding
comentarios bastante fuertes con respeto
an abuse of Ching FR that's why they
a un abuso de Ching FR por eso lo
banned him well let them finish banning
funaron pues que lo terminen de funar al
dan Flow but Danny Flow I don't give a
dan Flow pero el Danny Flow me vale
[ __ ] brother defining battles in such a
[__] brother definir de esta manera tan
simplistic way is  a mistake It's
simplista las batallas es un error Es
like if I said And it's wrong literally I'm going to
como si yo dijera Y es que mal literal
collect the
voy voy a recoger las las propias
people's own words they make
palabras de personas hacen todo el rato
the same cheap rhymes all the time d review
las mismas rimas baratas d review
always makes the same cheap criticisms
siempre hace las mismas críticas baratas
and it gives me a real cringe and it gives me a
y me da auténtico cringe y me da
real cringe it would be the same you
auténtico cringe sería lo mismo
understand it's a very simplistic way of being
entiendes es una manera muy simplista de
able to define any consideration of
poder definir cualquier consideración de
life I can apply it also the same it's not
la vida puedo aplicarlo también igual no
that Dallas's criticisms are
es que las críticas de Dallas son
cheap he always makes the same ones and they give me
baratas siempre hace las mismas y me dan
cringe let's see I understand that it can give you
cring a ver entiendo que te puede dar
certain freestylers and certain
según qué freestylers y según qué
battles it can give you cringe me too
batallas te puede dar cring a mí también
well it has its audience there are a lot of people
bueno tiene su público hay mucha gente
who consume that type of content
que que consume ese tipo de contenido
okay eh No There is something wrong dalla there are
vale eh No Ahí sí está mal dalla hay
enough good freestyles let's see tell me
bastantes freestyle buenos a ver decirme
one that I can put here an example
uno que yo pueda poner aquí un ejemplo
to see if I like them let's see it's what I
para ver si me gustan a ver es que es lo
told you before to tastes
que os he dicho antes para gustos
colors you know There will be people who may
colores sabes Habrá gente que pueda
think that I who know something that I like
pensar que yo que sé algo que me guste a
big brother Okay, well the cringe
mí gran hermano Vale pues que la cringe
or the heart programs and that's it and they
o los programas del corazón y ya está y
are tastes okay I see it about
son gustos vale yo lo veo lo de las
these battles and the rhymes and so on and I
batallas estas y las rimas y demás y
say Well, yes to me  I think a little more
digo Bueno a mí sí s pienso un poco más
like Dallas okay And then about
como el Dallas vale Y luego sobre lo de
fitting the rhyme by egg I mean if
encajar la rima por huevo o sea si si te
the rhyme comes out well you say it and if not you
sale la rima bien la dices y si no nada
know nothing there you say it That is true
sabes ahí ya dices tú Eso sí es verdad
that it is
que se
done I mean that is true do not take the
hace o sea eso sí es verdad no cogas la
word you change the accentuation and there
palabra le cambias la acentuación y ahí
the rhyme does not and if it does not come out to rhyme then
la rima no y si no sale a la rima pues
you put it anyway okay And then about everything
la metes igual vale Y luego sobre todo
that we have commented many times not
lo que hemos comentado muchas veces no
about justifying saying any
lo de justificar el decir cualquier
barbarity because this is free Then
barbaridad porque esto es free Entonces
since it is free you can say whatever
como es free se puede decir lo que sea
no Let's see benet jas let's see
no A ver benet jas a ver
benet okay But this has a lot of copy or
benet vale Pero esto tiene mucho copio o
what Let's see come on let's listen I
qué A ver venga vamos a escuchar yo que
know
sé
this always talents There are none
esto siempre talentos No
left you are in front of Buddha you have
quedan estás enfrente de Buda te has
brought your pen But that will not help
traído tu pluma Pero eso no ayudará
because against my sweats you will end up in
porque contra mis sudadas ya acabarás en
the
las
Bermuda shorts of the Good one that does not fit you
bermudas del Bueno del que no te queda
go thinking patterns to throw them
vete pensando patrones para tirarlos
fera separate a minute in six patterns
fera separate un minuto en seis patrones
of any I throw a whole minute and
de cualquiera yo tiro un minuto entero y
of those minutes There are none
de esos minutos No
left let's see I respect eh I mean they are
quedan a ver yo respeto eh o sea son
people's tastes each one understands
gustos de la gente cada uno se entiende
their taste and  your move I have one thing
en su gusto y su movida yo Ha una cosa
that I don't like and that's it, like you
que no no me gusta y y ya está o sea en
know, like I don't like it, I do
plan sabes o sea a mí no me gusta a mí
n't like it, okay, look, Uncle Shur
no me gusta vale mira el tío shur le
likes it, for example, no, Uncle Sur also
gusta por ejemplo no el tío Sur también
reacts to these things
se pone a reaccionar a estas cosas
a lot of times, no, I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't know, I
muchas veces yo no yo no me gusta no me
understand that you will have to
gusta yo que sé entiendo que tendrá que
have, you will have to have your skill, no
tener tendrás que tener tu habilidad no
also, and your art to be better or worse
también y tu arte para ser mejor o peor
and for that to come out, not there on
y que te salga eso no ahí en el
stage in front of the audience. I don't think it has to
escenario delante del público No creo
be improvised, no also, no, it's not
que tiene que ser improvisado no también
going, eh, it's not going, it's not
no que no va eh que no va que no va
rehearsed, no. I mean, what you have
ensayado no O sea que que que se te
to come up with on the fly,
tiene que ocurrir sobre la marcha
too. No man, well, you have to have
también No hombre pues tienes que tener
your art. Of course, Benet, it's crazy, let's
tu arte Claro que sí benet es una locura
see, but this, this is Benet and this is
a ver pero este este es benet y este es
the most reproduced moment.
el momento más reproducido
Don't get out of the funa, you already laughed at me,
no lárguense de la funa ya me reron
what networks? What networks? We are
ustedes qué redes Qué redes Nosotros
good, we are Dori, we will swim, we will
somos buenos somos Dori nadaremos
swim, champion of energy drinks, this
nadaremos campeón de energizantes este
son of a [ __ ]. The Red Bull that Benet won
hijo de [__] La Red Bull que ganó benet
was surely
seguro era sin
sugar-free, you won, it was 0, brother. Ah,
azúcar ganaste que era 0 hermano Ah
why haven't you won? And yours, which was
porque no has ganado y la tuya que era
the  new green flavor that they have released that they
el sabor verde nuevo que han sacado que
have released this seems
han sacado esto parece
excellent there are people who
excelente está hay gente a la que le
like it this occurs to me watch many battles
guste está me ocurre ve muchas batallas
but not all the battles are Flow
pero no todas las batallas son Flow
kinge we understand not all the battles
kinge entendemos no todas las batallas
are of rapper for example not all the
son de rapder por ejemp no todas las
battles are of saam not all the battles
batallas son de saam no todas las
are of well of X competitors
batallas son de bueno de X competidores
but it is that equally maybe surely Well
pero es que igual a lo mejor seguramente
there are other people who watch
Pues hay otras personas que ven los
these heart programs that I
programas estos del corazón que a mí me
like and they entertain me right
gustan y me entretienen no
and they will say all the time that it is cring or that
eh Y dirán todo el tiempo que es cring o
the heart press is cring Look
que la prensa del corazón es cring Mira
you see the videos that come out to me
veis los vídeos que me salen a mí
recommended look look Prince Harry has gone to see his father I don't know what I mean it's ...
yo eso justificarlo no es que esto es
I don't see it anymore, much less when you're
ya no lo veo yo y menos cuando estás
talking or attacking someone who's
hablando o atacando a alguien que está
outside of that world, you know, or about Garza,
fuera del mundillo ese sabes o de Garza
don't talk to me about Fight Club, don't
no me hablas del Club de la pelea no le
give the ball to Pele. Ah well, I understand
den el balón a pele Ah bueno entiendo
that that gives you cringe. Okay, that's normal
que eso te de cringe Okay eso es normal
that it gives you cringe, but not all
que te de cringe pero no todas las
battles are like that, there are very good battles, there
batallas son así hay batallas muy buenas
are iconic battles that I would also
hay batallas icónicas que además yo te
recommend you watch. Dallas. And you would probably
recomendaría ver Dalas Y seguramente te
like it a lot. The truth is, really, every
gustaría mucho la verdad de verdad cada
time I hear them, I say, God, I feel a
vez que les escucho digo Dios siento un
pain here in my chest every time
dolor aquí en el pecho cada vez que les
I hear them try to make new rhymes and
oigo intentar hacer rimas nuevas y
change the accentuation of the words, I just ca
cambiar la acentuación de las palabras
n't stand it in language. Yeah, let's
es que no lo soporto en el lenguaje Sí a
see, I understand where this is going, but no. I mean, it
ver entiendo por dónde va pero no O sea
's not a general dyssematic tonic, it doesn't
no es una tónica general dis semática no
talk about systoles and diastoles, for
habla de de las sístoles y diástoles por
example, kn kn, he did it a lot, I know
ejemplo kn kn lo hacía mucho yo sabes
that I come from a hunter Flow because you know
que vengo un Flow cazador porque sabes
that right now I'm a bird to
que ahora mismo soy un pájaro para
bring bird with bird, which is a
arrimar pájaro con pájaro que es una
troupe with a hunter, well, he changes the
trupa con cazador pues le cambia la
accentuation to a hunter, no, eh? Yes, yes, and he
acentuación a a cazador no eh Sí sí y lo
does it a lot.  I'll break these rappers
hace muchísimo le parto estos rappers
like Flow what will they say you know I do
rollo Flow qué dirá sabes Eso a mí
n't like that either there I have to give it to them
tampoco me gusta ahí se la tengo que dar
or rather for someone outside the battle it's
o sea para alguien ajen la batalla es
something that looks ugly no And for the people
algo que se ve feo no Y para la gente
who are typical of The battles you know
que es propio de Las batallas sabes en
personally to me And look No I'm a
lo personal a mí Y fíjate No yo soy un
very open guy about the issue of
tío muy abierto por el tema de las
mantic disson and that each one
disson mánticas y de que cada cual pores
rhymes as they consider the issue of
rime como considere el tema de la
accentuation That's why I prefer that you
acentuación Por eso yo prefiero que
rhyme in a mantic disson way rancio
rimes de manera disson mántica rancio
with Cancin I prefer that Ares So
con Canción Prefiero que la Ares Así que
doing rancio with Cancin you understand here is
hacer rancio con canción entiendes aquí
right but what happens What happens is that it
tiene razón pero qué pasa Qué pasa que
is far from reality Because the
está alejado de la realidad Porque la
vast majority of freestylers do not use
gran mayoría de freestylers no utilizan
this rhetorical figure that let's not forget
esta figura retórica que no olvidemos
that it is a rhetorical figure the hisol
que es una figura retórica la la hisol
of the diastol are rhetorical figures eh
de la diastol son figuras retóricas eh
now that they are well to taste the truth
ahora que queden bien a gustos la verdad
Spanish changes a lot to say this one that is
español cambia mucho decir esta que está
eh eh I have the power Neither this one nor this one
eh eh yo tengo la potestad Ni esta ni
these rappers constantly
está estos raperillos constantemente
modify the accentuation of the words
modifican la acentuación de las palabras
so that it rhymes better with the other
para que rime mejor con las otras
words that  they have said it's not true it
palabras que han dicho no es verdad no
's not true I mean it's not true removing a
es verdad O sea no es verdad quitando
couple of rappers I mean who does this
par de rappers es decir quién hace esto
normally very few use the subject
normalmente muy pocos se emplean el tema
of the hiso diastole because as
de las hiso diástole porque como
unbearable it gives me OCD I really feel
insoportable me da Toc de verdad siento
cring every time I listen to them I think
cring cada vez que les escucho creo que
0.1 times that I have seen some of
un 0,1 veces que he visto alun vez de
these little rappers do their
estos raperillos hacer sus
rapper their freestyles recci
raper sus freestyles reacci
abnet Borja we have already put King I don't know if
abnet Borja ya hemos puesto Rey no sé si
the super chat has delayed you you say
te ha [__] el super chat dices
freestyles it is freestyle 1% of the times
freestyles es freestyle 1% de las veces
that I have seen some of these
que he visto algun vez de estos
little rappers do their freestyles notio
raperillos hacer sus freestyles notio
true cring listening to them Because
verdadero cring escuchándoles Porque
also always in all the
además siempre en todas las
battles Hi Javi do you know where
batallas Hola Javi sabes dónde está
laser is in the town or
láser en el pueblo o
something
algo
no this afternoon he called me and told me he
no esta tarde me llamó y me dijo que
was at the mercadona Don't worry
estaba en el mercadona No te preocupes
what the [ __ ] do I know doesn't he keep doing his
yo qué [__] sé no sigue haciendo sus
things that he does there that they do they use
cosas esas que hace allas que hacen usan
and repeat the same rhymes over and over again I
y repiten las mismas rimas una y otra
mean no it's not true either I mean it
vez O sea no no es cierto tampoco O sea
's not true It's not true that there are rhymes
no es cierto No es cierto que hay rimas
that are repeated yes there are concepts that are
que se repiten sí que hay conceptos que
repeated  Yes, battles
se repiten sí que siempre las batallas
are always like that, no, not necessarily because
son así no No necesariamente porque el
finite language is also true. Yes, I hear
lenguaje finito también Sí oyo el
finite language and there are rhymes that are
lenguaje finito y hay rimas que se
evidently repeated, but rarely
repiten evidentemente pero rara vez
are all the battles the same, dude,
todas las batallas son las mismas tibón
if they face each other for the fifth time, well, it
si se enfrentan por de quinta vez pues
can be repetitive, and there are issues
si puede ser repetitivo y hay cuestiones
that constantly fall back on the same
que recaen todo el rato en un mismo
argument, for example,
argumento tal o por ejemplo a Mister
calling Mister a drunk or a monkey are
llamarle de borracho o a re mono son
things that go on for a long
cosas que se se dilatan mucho en el
time and constantly, yes, they
tiempo y constantemente sí pueden
can refer to the same resource and it is said in a way, like, in a way, they say the same thing, they talk about how they are going to benefit your mother, 99% of them, and this is not true either. This happened in 2006, in 2008, the thing about the other guy's mother,
2006 en el 2008 lo de la mamá del otro
well, it kind of came to light a
ya pues pues como que trascendió hace
long time ago, it was an argument widely used at the
muchos era un argumento muy utilizado en
time, but it gives me the feeling.
su época pero a mí me da la sensación
Yes, but well, I think that I think that this
Sí pero bueno yo creo que yo creo que
thing about everyone saying I'm going to sleep with
esto de que todos dicen me voy a tirar
your mother is
tu madre es
[Music]
[Música]
like an example, eh, generalizing
como como un ejemplo eh generalizando un
the type of expressions a bit. I mean, not
poco el tipo de expresiones O sea no
literally, all the songs
literalmente que todas las canciones
have I'm going to sleep with your mother.
tengan me voy a tirar tu madre A lo
Maybe there's another one that says I'm going to sleep with
mejor hay otra que dice me voy a tirar
your sister or how hot
tu hermana o qué buena se está poniendo
your sister is getting something like that no I mean the
tu hermana alguna cosa así no O sea el
tone and the type of phrases and the type of
tono y el tipo de frases y el tipo de
type of
tipo de
expressions Like for example Danny
expresiones Como por ejemplo la de Danny
Flow's would be for the friends of well
Flow le tocaría a las amigas de bueno
that one apart from the vulgar
esa aparte ya de de los vulgares
even Scandalous for the subject minors
incluso Escandalosa por el tema menores
no
no
but alas he has really seen a couple of
pero alas realmente ha visto un par de
battles and he is talking about the battles
batallas y está hablando de Las batallas
and sentences in a way that
y y sentencias de una manera un poco
for me he is quite ignorant quite
para mí peca de ignorante bastante en
truly And look that for other things he
verdad Y fíjate que para otras cosas
is very based and I think that I give it to him in
está muy basado y creo que se la doy en
many other things Dallas has
muchas otras cosas Dallas ha
generalized first with the way of
generalizado primero con la manera de
executing rhymes which is the histories and
ejecutar rimas que es las histories y
the diores that use them very few
las diores que las emplean muy poco
freestylers the subject of your mother your mother
freestylers el tema de tu madre tu madre
your mother it is rare to see today a
tu madre es raro ver a día de hoy un
freestyler abuse so much the
freestyler abusar tanto de de la
other's relative It is rare that they
parienta del otro Es raro es que te
pull your old lady on you it is already done in battles
tiren de tu viejita ya en batallas se
Yes but it is a resource more not the
hace Sí pero es un recurso más no las
times and by the way stories aside in
veces y por cierto historias aparte en
the time when it was fashionable to
la época en la que estaba de moda
tell me any barbarity some of
decirme cualquier barbaridad algunos de
these  Infectious trash rappers were
estos raperillos basura infectos se
dedicated to doing these
dedicaban a hacer estas batallas de
rhyme battles literally But why does he do
rimas literalmente Pero por qué hace
rhyme battles between quotes Why
batallas de rimas entre comillas Por qué
freestyle rhymes between quotes are not
freestyle de rimas entre comillas no son
free and are rim br mentioning me, that is,
fre y son rim br mencionándome o sea
they fought with each other and what they did was
peleaban con el otro y lo que hacían era
throw garbage at me that neither does it happen to
tirarme basura a m que niqu ya también
me too, pasol sias was present there
me pasa estaba ahí presente pasol sias
Twitter you do a favor to everyone now but Bro it
Twitter haces un favor a tod ya pero Bro
makes me laugh Because you also took have
me hace gracia Porque además has cogido
you seen the screen not Porta versus
habéis visto la pantalla no Porta versus
Dallas beyond the
Dallas sea más allá del recurso de
battle resource that ah they put the topics and
batalla que ah que te ponen los temas y
you have to resort to that let's
tú tienes que recurrir a eso a
see let's put
ver vamos a poner
Dallas free Style or rather and there will be a
Dallas free Style o sea y habrá un
lot
montón
No here is Mister ego's that this
No aquí está el de Mister ego que esto
was like what Quesada justified to me at the
fue como lo que me justificó en su
time that was like no no
momento el Quesada que era como no no
but it's that it's free and I was left
pero es que es free y yo me quedé
Sorry Good night Javi how are you
Perdona Buenas noches Javi cómo estás
How was your day today I hope you are well I
Cómo fue tu día hoy Espero que bien Me
like your content and you are a tall person
gusta tu contenido y eres alta persona
a kiss I would like you to send a greeting
un bes me gustaría que mandes un saludo
to a friend named Black Rober let's see
a un amigo llamado Black Rober a ver
I'm trying to find the rhyme Black
estoy intentando encontrar la rima Black
Robert okay I don't  I'm eating no
Robert vale no me estoy comiendo ninguna
[ __ ] a greeting Black
[__] un saludo Black
Robert I'm answering a super
Robert estoy contestando un super
thanks I'm answering a super
gracias estoy contestando un super
Thanks
Gracias
eh Black rovers I've eaten something I've
eh Black rovers me he comido algo me he
eaten some
comido algún
trolling this no Mister ego marb This was
troleo esto no Mister ego marb Esto fue
tremendous that I come I have all the talent
tremendo que vengo Tengo todo el talento
have you seen trunk like Chana I don't know what you
has visto tronco como Chana no sé qu has
said about the panorama I don't know what you said about the
dicho del panorama no sé qu has dicho
panorama you are a minor
del panorama tú eres una menor de edad
yela they are not going to call you dasas Osa that
yela no se le van a llamar dasas Osa esa
reference I get the truth that to
referencia Pillo la verdad que de
recognize that it has turned out very well for you
reconocer que muy bien te ha
But I don't know what I'm going to do
quedado Pero yo no sé lo que voy a hacer
I want the writers of I also want
Quiero los escritores de También quiero
those of es gre
los del es gre
and
y
mat anyway let's see wait there's sure to be
mat en fin a ver a ver espera que seguro
[Music]
[Música]
more I don't understand these things
más Yo es que estas cosas no no las
Uy the Track do you remember the
entiendo Uy el Track os acordáis del de
track do
track
you remember this well
os acordáis de esto bueno Esto lo
This was deleted by the
borró esto lo borró el
driak God This this was to
driak Dios Esta esta estaba para
report him eh the song This eh
denunciarle eh la canción Esta eh
committed vd vendetta is my ideology
comprometido vd vendeta es mi ideología
debts are paid I'll send you the receipt it's
las deudas se pagan Te paso el recibo es
time to ask yourself why all your exes
hora de preguntarte por qué todas tus ex
always regret  having
siempre se arrepienten de haberte
met you your first partner accused you of
conocido tu primera pareja te acusó de
abuse and no one believed her for acting
maltrato y nadie la creyó por hacerte el
helpless until on the internet that you would
desvalido hasta que en internet que
hit your girlfriend if you saw her
pegarías a tu novia si la vieras
dancing with a stranger the second
bailando con un desconocido la segunda
was Ingrid you despicable vermin you died
fue Ingrid alimaña despreciable teiste
of the cancer that took her mother God
del cáncer que se llevó a su madre Dios
that my mother that song eh Ugh it gives me
eso madre mía esa canción eh Uf me da
this thing listening to it today that
esta cosa escucharlo a día de hoy ese
piece that we have put eh Javi crack yourself
trozo que hemos puesto eh Javi rífate tú
a
una
rhyme I'm Javi
rima Soy Javi
Oliveira I weigh
oliveira peso
1.80 my name is Javi
1.80 me llamo Javi
Oliveira Because my grandfather was also
oliveira Porque mi abuelo también se
called
llamaba
Oliveira pum pum
oliveira pum pum
pum I'm going to explain now it's that
pum lo voy a explicar ahora es que
directly dasas was thematic Porta
directamente dasas era temática Porta
versus Dalas was thematic piece of
versus Dalas era temática pedazo de
bololo if you leave Twitter you're doing
bololo si te marchas de Twitter le haces
everyone a favor you can send
un favor a todos puedes mandarle
condolences to Piera condolences to
condolencias a Piñera condolencias a
Piera a kiss Andy Thank you very much I don't know
Piñera un beso Andy Muchas gracias No sé
what's going on in Piera you've been
qué es lo que pasa en Piñera me estáis
giving me a lot of messages lately of Oh
dando últimamente muchos mensajes de Ay
support this support that and it's like you know I do
apoya esto apoy lo otro y es como sabes
n't understand it
no lo entiendo
[Music]
[Música]
and this rhyme in particular that he put up well
e esta rima en concreto que ha puesto
no  It's okay if Dallas blocks you or
pues no pasa nada si te bloquea Dallas o
if you mess with D on Twitter, I mean, it's
si te metes con D en Twitter o sea es
nonsense. At the end of the day, what I
una tontería Al fin y al cabo no yo lo
find strong is when they put you like
que veo fuerte es cuando te ponen como
him and tell you things about being a pedophile and
el a decirte cosas de de pedófilo y
things like that, you can't be ashamed of yourself
cosas de esas no vergüenza ajena puedes
and how cowardly do you have to be
dar y cómo de cobarde tienes que ser
to throw yourself at someone,
para tirarle a alguien con ni siquiera
you're not even fighting just to
te estás peleando únicamente para
win the applause of the public, Danan. Don't
ganarte el aplauso del público danan No
think you're that important, you know, I mean, this
te creas tan importante sabes o sea esto
happens to me too and it happens
a mí me pasa también y le pasa
to absolutely any
absolutamente a cualquier personaje
public figure. I mean, using a resource, in
público O sea que utilicen un recurso en
this case, you or I in a battle, as a
este caso tú o yo en una batalla como
resource, is still a resource that
recurso no deja de ser es un recurso que
they play with, for or against,
ellos juegan o A favor o en contra al
just as they could have used you in a
igual que te han podido utilizar de
negative way, they can also
manera negativa también lo pueden
use it in a positive way within the
utilizar de manera positiva dentro de la
fiction of the battles themselves. Then
ficción de las propias batallas luego
each person, beyond the character,
cada persona más allá del personaje
because, of course, in this case, I have put, uh,
porque Claro en este caso he puesto eh
a rhyme by Walls, but Gines, who is the
una rima de Walls pero ginés que es la
person, will be able to have an opinion about
persona podrá tener una opinión formada
you, both negative or positive, you would have to
de ti tanto negativa o positiva habría
ask him, you know, but of course,
que preguntarle sabes pero claro al
just as they have used rhymes by Dallas, they have
igual que han utilizado rimas de Dallas
talked about chocas, they have talked about
han hablado del chocas han hablado de
energy, they have talked about me  they've talked about
energía han hablado de mí han hablado de
gref they've talked about ibai from all over the
gref han hablado de ibai de todo el
world but yeah of course but it's that when
mundo pero sí claro pero es que cuando
you talk about chocas Let's see
hablas del chocas A ver vamos a ver
some that they've said about
alguna que hayan dicho del
chocas the terms are not the
chocas los términos no son los
same the terms are not the same damn
mismos los términos no son los mismos
Look at the shocka
[__] Mira el shocka
you
tú
that ended with a persuasive text
que acabase con un texto persuasivo
making good structures is something that I
hacer buenas estructuras es algo que me
love I find myself entering this
encanta me encuentro me adentro en este
pattern man Look at
patrón tío Mira el
chocas and I'm going to put it on for you I'm going to
chocas y os la voy a poner os la voy a
put it on for you I'm going to put it on for you they are simply Well
poner os la voy a poner simplemente son
nothing 30 seconds It's that a lot of
Pues nada 30 segundos Es que esto mucha
people don't know this and I'm going to put it on for you I'm
Peña y os la voy a poner os la voy a
going to put it on for you they are simply Well
poner os la voy a poner simplemente son
nothing 30 seconds It's that a lot of
Pues nada 30 segundos Es que esto mucha
people don't know this I've been I've been
Peña no lo sabe yo llevo yo llevo
rapping since I was 13 14 years old and I've
rapeando desde que tengo 13 14 años y
been writing lyrics for
llevo escribiendo letras desde hace
many years eh I know a lot more about rap than
muchos años eh sé mucho más de rap que
probably all of you me every
probablemente todos vosotros yo cada
night that I went out in Salamanca I would start
noche que salía en Salamanca era empezar
drinking and freestyling Maybe an
a beber y hacer freestyle A lo mejor una
hour doing Freestyle or two hours
hora haciendo Freestyle o dos horas
doing Freestyle while we drank at
haciendo Freestyle mientras bebíamos de
parties and then we went to party  to
botellón y luego nos íbamos de fiesta a
be a hooligan out there and all that [ __ ] Well, that I really like it
hacer el gamberro por ahí y eso [__]
I
Pues que que que me Mola mucho me Mola
really like it and I've been listening to it for a
mucho y que lo llevo escuchando desde
long time and for me it's very
hace mucho tiempo y para mí es muy
exciting [ __ ] that appearing in something so
ilusionante [__] que salir en algo tan
important no I hope not I won't
importante no Espero que no yo no
descend of course I won't descend
desciendo desde luego yo no desciendo
because I put my balls my mother
porque yo pongo mis huevos mi madre Me
tells me it's nothing it's a game mom Tell
dice no pasa nada es un juego mam Dile a
Lebron James that this is a
Lebron James que esto es un
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
game the
juego el
same the same term they use for
mismo el mismo término utilizan para el
choga as with Dallas the same the
choga que con el Dallas los mismos el
same type of expressions because it's
mismo tipo de expresiones porque es lo
normal or rather in a fictional world where they
normal o sea en un mundo ficticio donde
improvise at the moment It depends on whether
se improvisa al momento Depende si
you slander I don't
calumnias no
think so students I don't think Well then that I am in
creo sí que alumnas No creo Bueno pues
a judicial process you will go
que llevo un proceso judicial daras
ahead with with the people who
adelante con con la gente que la
dedicated a rhyme to it let's see I
dedicado una rima a ver yo es que
understand I am not a judge but I understand
entiendo yo no soy juez pero yo entiendo
that in a
que en un marco
fictional framework Because it is still
eh ficticio Porque no deja de ser
fictional that are the battles it is that
ficticio que son las batallas es que que
as if you tell me I am not going to denounce the
como si me dices no voy a denunciar al
Undertaker because he said eh that he is going to
Undertaker porque ha dicho eh que va a
kill whoever he sees on the street  See what
matar a quien vea por la calle a ver lo
Undertaker said standing in a ring
ha dicho Undertaker subido en un ring
with a WWE microphone I understand that it
con un micrófono de la WWE entiendo que
's part of his character and it's part of
es parte de su personaje y es parte de
the characteristics of the Villain that he's
las características del Villano que está
playing at that moment for example
interpretando en ese momento por ejemplo
no pu it's the same thing happens in the battles no and I
no pu es lo mismo pasa las batallas no y
also tell you the part about alas that he
te digo también la parte de alas de que
's tired and he must be fed up with
está fatigado y tiene que estar hasta
everyone
los [__] de que todo el mundo le le
having thrown at him and continue to throw at them and more in an
haya tirado y les siga tirando y más de
unfair way on certain issues that we
manera injusta en ciertos temas no que
all
todos
know Sebastian Piera was a
sabemos Sebastian Piñera era un
former president of Chile but you
expresidente de chile pero es que me
're talking to me about things that I don't know
estáis hablando de cosas que yo no sé
my son you're talking to me about some
hijo mío me estáis hablando de unas
little things that I don't know what do you want me to
cosillas que no lo sé qué quieres que te
tell you let's see what else some
diga a ver qué más alguna
alana canceled for collaborating with
alana cancelada por colaborar con
wesc
wesc
alana do you remember alana this was the
alana os acordáis de alana esta fue la
girl who asked uncle Sur to delete a
chica que le pidió al tío Sur borrar un
video
vídeo
because she yelled at her boyfriend in the car do you
porque le gritó al novio en el coche os
remember Today is the
acordáis Hoy es el
day Thank you for responding anyway being
día Gracias por responder igual siendo
honest it depresses me not seeing laser what do you
honesto me deprime no ver a láser que me
advise me Well you have the other what's
aconseja Pues tienes al otro cómo se
the other's name the one who is now with
llama el otro el que está ahora con la
Peppa Beltrn okay I don't know  to
Peppa Beltrán vale Yo que sé para para
fix more or less if you like that
apañar más o menos si te gusta esos
content Well you might also like
contenidos Pues también te puede valer
Alana who appeared on the channel a few
alana que salió en el canal hace unos
months ago for yelling at her partner
meses por gritarle a su pareja en
live is being canceled for
directo está siendo cancelada por
collaborating with Westcol Yesterday it was not a
colaborar con westcol Ayer no era
King collaboration or promotion they are
colaboración de la King ni promoción la
criticizing her since she gets along
están criticando ya que ella se lleva
with Ari and Juan
con Ari y Juan
Also because Westcol you are with Barca
Además porque wescol tuo bef con Barca
for the same reason let's see truth How
por el mismo motivo a ver verdad Qué
strange no How strange this collaboration W did
raro no Qué raro esta colaboración W
you see that Wes with Santos Ftbol Club it is
viste que wes con Santos Fútbol Club le
easy for him to play the first date of the
toca fácil la primera fecha de la
Kinsley Yes you know that the first game
kinsley Sí sabes que la primer partido
I have to count tar Ranisa Fbol Club how [ __ ] disgusting it is
me toca cont tar ranisa fúbol Club qué
going to be the game where he is going to
[__] asco va a ser el partido donde más
vite me the most always as soon as that
me va a vitar siempre apenas empiece ese
intro starts as soon as it comes out Uy Vitar me
intro apenas lo va saliendo Uy Me vitar
so many times hon on top of me that I am going to have to
tantas veces hón encima mío que me va a
have a towel next to me I ca
tocar tener una toalla al lado
n't believe it's happening to me bro
yo no puedo creer que me toque así bro
don't underestimate who is
no subestimes es que quién está
underestimating me I'm just saying that I'm going to throw
subestimando yo solo estoy diciendo que
up I can't say that I'm going to throw up
me vo a vomitar no puedo decir que me va
I am not underestimating
a vomitar yo no estoy subestimando
absolutely anyone I'm just
absolutamente a nadie yo solo estoy
saying that as soon as they are coming out
diciendo que apenas y que están saliendo
on the field I am going to  vomit many times, I
a la cancha voy a vomitar muchas veces o
mean, how strange, no Good morning, I see that there
sea Qué raro no Buenos días veo que se
was a mess because of the bet and the
hizo un desmadre por la apuesta y la
collaboration yesterday. I understand and respect that it
colaboración ayer entiendo y respeto que
is not pleasant For some people
no sea del agrado Para algunas personas
I am still me and I do not stop being me To
Yo sigo siendo yo y no dejo de ser yo
play one day with whoever eh Let's
Por jugar un día con quien sea eh A
see, I also get along, maybe I can
ver yo también me llevo a lo mejor puedo
collaborate with someone, someone with
colaborar con alguien que alguien con
whom I get along, a friend of mine eh Don't
quien me llevo algún colega mío eh No se
get along, I mean, it's a little childish, not the one there is
lleve o sea es un poco infantil no el
But look how this one doesn't talk
que hay Pero mira como este no se habla
to the other Well, I don't either, not to
con el otro Pues yo tampoco no hasta
certain levels, man, for
ciertos niveles hombre por
example, what can I say if you have
ejemplo qué te digo yo si tú le has
told a friend of mine or a friend of mine
dicho a un amigo mío o a un colega mío
that he is a rapist Well, I'm not going
que es un violador Pues lo mismo no voy
to talk to you, but that is a bit
a habar contigo pero eso es un poco
logical and evident and I think that you have to be
lógico y evidente y creo que hay que ser
coherent, no, eh Now another thing is that
coherente no eh Ahora otra cosa es que
you talk to people that people with whom
tú te hables con gente que gente con la
you talk do not get along or
que tú te hables no se lleve bien o
have their problems, not as is the case,
Tenga sus problemas no como es el caso
okay, I don't know how friendly Lana will be with
vale No sé qué tan amiga será lana de
Hari
hari
Gameplays and with
Gameplays y de
Juan either, what W told her Let's
Juan tampoco lo que le dijo W A ver a
see what wcar told her Gameplay was
ver lo que le dijo wcar Gameplay era
ugly, well  It was very
feo bueno era muy
free Of course taking into account
gratuito Es que claro teniendo en cuenta
that wcol that is the least that dispatches I
que wcol eso es lo mínimo que despacha
understand that you do things
entiendo que ustedes hagan las cosas a
your way but I want to take it
su modo pero yo me las quiero llevar
easy I want the kin to be an
tranqui quiero que la kin sea una
experience from which I take the
experiencia de la cual me lleve los
best memories once a wise man said
mejores recuerdos una vez un sabio dijo
your enemies are not my enemies I am not one to
tus enemigos no son mis enemigos yo no
try to convince people to
soy de tratar de convencer a los de que
like the same people as
le caigan más las mismas personas que a
me more I prefer that they judge it by their
mí prefiero que la juzguen por sus
own experiences everyone has
propias experiencias cada quien tiene
their reasons and way of being here
sus razones y formma de ser aquí
basically what she is telling you is that
básicamente lo que te está diciendo es
her friend Ari if they are
que que su amiga Ari si es que son
friends is that let's see people on the internet do
amigos es que a ver la gente de internet
not often believe that
tampoco muchas veces os creéis que
because we have coworkers
porque tengamos compañeros de trabajo
people with whom we collaborate more or less
gente con la que colaboramos más o menos
regularly let's see It is not necessarily
habitualmente a ver No necesariamente es
a
un
friend A friend is someone in
amigo Un amigo es alguien de la vida
real life with whom you have let's see I do
real con quien tiene a ver yo sí que
have friends on the internet okay I have
tengo amigos en internet vale Yo hay
some people very few with the fingers
algunas personas muy pocas con los dedos
of one hand Surely I have too many eh that
de una mano Seguramente me sobran eh que
if I can say that they are friends because I know
si puedo decir que son amigos porque sé
that I can trust and that they will be there
que puedo confiar y que van a estar
until the end you know but there are times when you
hasta el final sabes pero hay veces que
see a lot of me with some youtubers with
me veis muchos con algunos youtubers con
that I collaborate and say Friend Friend we
los que yo colaboro y decí Amigo Amigo
were talking about this the other day let's see a
esto lo hablábamos el otro día a ver un
friend for me is a person who knows
amigo para mí es una persona que conoce
things about my life eh knows things about my
cosas de mi vida eh conoce cosas de mi
environment doesn't know me knows me You know
entorno no conoce me conoce a mí Sabes
knows when I'm good when I'm bad I
sabe cuando estoy bien cuando estoy mal
know something else
yo que sé algo más
no Hey another thing is that you have a
no Oye otra cosa es que tengas una
person that you really like with whom
persona que te caiga muy bien con la que
you have a lot of chemistry for collaborations
tengas mucha química para colaboraciones
or that more or less you have affinities in
o que más o menos tengáis afinidades en
common no that maybe she is not a friend
común no que a lo mejor no es una amiga
maybe Ari Gameplay is a person
a lo mejor Ari Gameplay es una persona
with whom she is interested in collaborating for x
con la que le interesa colaborar por x
reason okay And they are collaborations that
motivo vale Y son colaboraciones que les
interest them both and outside okay and she doesn't give a
interesan a ambas y fuera vale y le sud
damn that this one got involved with
toda la pipa que este se haya metido con
her without more now I also tell you I see it
ella sin más ahora también te digo veo
quite
bastante
likely their partners yes they are very good friends
probable sus parejas sí son muy amigos
Barca and Juan No no yes yes it is strange from what I
Barca y Juan No no sí sí es extraña por
see quite likely that okay
lo que veo bastante probable que vale a
she doesn't give a damn what this one
ella le suda toda la pipa lo que este le
said to Ari and Juan But I see it
haya dicho a Ari y a Juan Pero veo
quite likely
bastante probable
that and Juan if they close doors to
que que y Juan si le cierren puertas a
lana I see it quite likely that Ari and
lana veo bastante probable que Ari y
Juan do close the doors to her to
Juan sí que le cieren las puertas a ella
never return  collaborate with her
para para no volver a colaborar con ella
more in fact I think it's going to be like that we're
más de hecho creo que va a ser así vamos
almost 100% it's going to be
casi al 100% va a ser
like that and well come on one more topic
así y bueno venga un temita más esta
tonight and I'm going okay he's telling me
noche y ya me voy vale me está diciendo
here that plex has responded to the
por aquí que plex ha respondido a la
controversy to what controversy friend Play is
polémica a que polémica amigo Play está
being canceled for this tiktok where
siendo cancelado por este tiktok donde
someone at the airport asks for likes
alguien en el aeropuerto le pide likes
to go to his
para ir a su
house to
casa a
see plex how many likes and you invite me to the
ver plex cuántos likes y me invitas a la
Epic
Epic
House to the Epic
House a la Epic
House npc
House npc
npc one sandwich
npc uno bocadillo
yes What is it No thanks
sí Qué es No gracias
Oh at least show the car you
Ah por lo menos enseña el coche que te
bought no or
compraste no o
something I'll take it as a nolex a million
algo Lo tomaré como un nolex un millón
Goodbye Okay
Adiós Vale
thanks It's a joke in the end he said
gracias Es una broma al final ha dicho
about a
lo de un
million
millón
It's a
Es una
joke let's go also what I'm telling you that
broma vamos además que te digo yo que
this in the ti is going to be fulfilled
esto en el ti se va a cumplir el millón
look look it's already been
mira mira ya lleva
757,000 how long are we
757.000 de cuánto tiempo estamos
talking about in Tito where does it say
hablando en Tito dónde
in Tito where does it say the date uncle
pone en Tito dónde pone la la fecha tío
entio never puts the date of where
entio nunca pone la fecha de donde se
the videos are uploaded no let's see a
suben los vídeos no a ver una
joke he made it like the joke no like I don't
broma ha hecho como la gracia no de no
want to invite you no I don't answer you but
te quiero invitar no no te contesto pero
then in the end  he said a million
luego al final ha dicho un millón
Goodbye
Adiós
okay he's going to get it
vale lo va a conseguir
besides How many days can
además Cuántos días puede llevar
this take to continue
esto seguir
also I'll also tell you one thing eh the
además también te digo una cosa eh el
thing about the
tema de las
houses whether it's a youtuber's house or whatever it
casas sea una casa de youtuber o sea lo
is I'm not telling you that he's
que sea no te digo yo a ti que sí que lo
going to invite him And the thing is that he made her feel
va a invitar Y es que la ha puesto en el
uncomfortable it was yesterday luare tells me let's
compromiso es de ayer me dice luare a
see he made her feel uncomfortable he didn't
ver lo ha puesto en el compromiso no le
tell her no he acted like it was funny
ha dicho que no ha hecho como la gracia
Not here eating a sandwich ignoring him and
No aquí de comer bocadillo ignorándolo y
all But in the end he said a million
demás Pero al final ha dicho un millón
okay it's like you
vale
shouldn't even want to go to
es que ni siquiera deberías querer ir a
anyone's house
la casa de nadie
dude you
tío
know the houses no dude I don't know you
sabes las casas no tío yo que sé
know but well it's a youtuber's house he
sabes pero bueno es una casa de youtuber
's a kid either hab there are many
es un chiquillo tampoco hab hay muchas
times when they are not aware the other day
veces que no son conscientes el otro día
gref for example also had an
gref por ejemplo también tuvo un
episode no where people showed up
episodio no que se le presentó la gente
at the door of the house and they were
en la puerta de la casa y le estaban
asking for a photo and all that no I think it
pidiendo foto y demás no que creo que
was precisely with plex because
era precisamente con plex porque estaba
plex was in the house
plex en la casa
[Music]
[Música]
eh
eh En
Anyway let's see what plex said we've been
fin a ver qué ha dicho plex llevamos 79
traveling the world for 79 days Okay Ah plex
días viajando por el mundo Ok Ah plex
end right now Well I think it's  to
termina ya mismo Bueno creo que va al
Hormiguero this week I don't know what
Hormiguero esta semana no sé qué
day Hormiguero is going but I don't know what day it's
día va Hormiguero pero no sé qué día
going I don't know if it will be tomorrow or even the day after tomorrow
va no sé si será mañana incluso eh
and it ends in
mañana pasado y termina en
[Music]
[Música]
one
un
we are ending in a
estamos termina en una
party Well I think it ends this
fiesta Pues creo que termina este fin de
weekend what happens is that it was extended 5
semana lo que pasa es que se amplió 5
days because I don't know
días porque no sé
what but but it ends right now Okay
qué pero pero termina ya mismo Okay
we arrived after a flight from Helsinki or
llegamos después de un vuelo de helsin o
where the hell it was from Italy or I don't know
de dónde [__] era de Italia o no sé de
where from Rome exhausted to Barcelona we
dónde de Roma reventados a Barcelona
arrived in Barcelona after 79 days
llegamos a Barcelona después de 79 días
of Spanish travel exhausted well all
de viaje español reventados bueno todos
dry 12 at night after all
secos 12 de la noche después de todo el
day recording all day traveling
día grabando todo el día viajando
we arrived and there's a very nice guy By
llegamos y hay un chaval muy Majo Por
the way The guy like I have
cierto El Chaval en plan yo no tengo
nothing against the guy okay but
nada en contra del chaval vale pero e
okay there was a guy that I don't know how he had
vale había un chaval que no sé cómo
found out that we were arriving
había descubierto que est que llegábamos
in Barcelona that day not even I
a Barcelona ese día ni siquiera yo lo
knew that we were arriving in Barcelona that day
sabía que llegábamos a Barcelona ese día
well The guy knew it too and we
bueno El chaval también lo sabía e
arrived there well with The guy well
llegamos ahí bueno con El chaval pues
very Cool Nice such we were recording with
muy Guay Majo tal estuvimos grabando con
him jopa gave him his cap after
él jopa le regaló su gorra después de
being easily 10 minutes  and there with the
estar fácilmente 10 minutos y ahí con El
guy who's cool and all because the
chaval de tranquis y tal porque la
truth is that we liked him and we already know
verdad que nos cayó bien y ya sabemos
that we are as we are with everyone
que somos como somos con todo el mundo
who sees us, I mean if you
que nos ve o sea si alguna vez nos
've ever seen us on the street you've
habéis visto por la calle nos habéis
asked us for a photo that's what I say The guy
pedido una foto eso digo yo El chaval
how did he know that this one was at the
cómo sabía que este estaba en el
airport How can he know that you know That
aeropuerto Cómo puede saber eso sabréis
we're normal guys with
Que que somos chavales normales con
you eh Let's see Around the World in
vosotros eh A ver La Vuelta al Mundo en
80 Days I understand that it's not going to be
80 días Yo entiendo que no va
absolutely live I imagine that
absolutamente en directo me imagino que
for editing reasons it will take at least
por tema de edición mínimo tardará irá
one day which will be more or less the same as what
con un día que será más o menos lo mismo
we will do when I'm in
que haremos nosotros cuando esté yo en
Thailand we are aware that I have
Tailandia somos conscientes de que me
days left we are aware that I have
días somos conscientes de que me faltan
barely 10
apenas 10
days left we have
días tenemos eso
assumed that I
asumido
ask There are days that it's on the same day
pregunto Hay días que es en el mismo día
but how complicated right
pero qué complicado no
So how complicated let's see I
Entonces qué complicado a ver yo
understand that when I'm in Thailand it
entiendo que cuando yo esté en Tailandia
will be one day late I imagine not I mean
irá con un día de retraso me imagino no
I will send him it's that I don't know the
O sea yo le mandaré es que no sé los
schedules yet I don't have the schedules very
horarios todavía no tengo los horarios
well very well assimilated how
mu bien muy bien asimilados cómo van a
the schedules will be let's see I understand that
ser los horarios a ver entiendo que
now what time what  time is now in
ahora qué hora qué hora es ahora en
Thailand right now in Thailand it's
Tailandia ahora mismo en Tailandia son
9 in the morning It's earlier than
las 9 de la mañana Es antes
here it's a few
que es antes que aquí son unas cuantas
hours earlier than here well yes it's
de horas antes que aquí pues si son las
9 in the morning let's see if I'm not
9 de la mañana a ver si no me
mistaken I understand that the night
equivoco yo entiendo que la noche
before the night before I sent the
antes la noche antes yo le he mandado el
video to these
vídeo a esta
people let's say the night before it
gente pongamos que la noche antes
's about 10 hours earlier of course
son unas 10 horas antes
I understand that these people are almost up
claro Yo entiendo que esta gente es casi
to date because it's almost up to date really Let's
al día porque es casi al día en verdad A
see not up to date obviously but of
ver no al día al día evidentemente pero
course
claro
m I will send them the videos when I
m Yo le mandaré los vídeos cuando me
go to
vaya para la
bed and for the Editors it's
cama y para los Editores es el
noon so most likely at
mediodía entonces muy probablemente por
night at the time that you're
noches a la hora que estáis
used to there being live at
acostumbrados a que haya directo por las
night you will have the
noches tendréis el
episode what happens is that I do
episodio lo que pasa es que sí que
understand that it will be late in
entiendo que irá con retraso en la vida
real life in the sense that I think that of
real en el sentido de que yo creo que de
everything that I record each day not
todo lo que vaya grabando cada día no va
just one episode will come out I understand that
a salir solo un episodio entiendo que
several episodes will come out of everything
van saliendo varios episodios de todo lo
that is recorded during the
que se grabe en el
day but no I can't know I have no
día pero no no lo puedo saber no tengo
idea em I'll take it I'll buy a
ni idea em yo cojo me compro un bocata
ham sandwich I'm already leaving after
de jamón ya me estoy yendo después de
be there already all exhausted there with
estar ahí ya todos reventados ahí con
chal for a while and I'm leaving and I
chal un rato y yo me estoy yendo y
hear Hey plex one last thing I turn like this
escucho Oye plex una última cosa me giro
The kid puts his phone on me like this
así El chaval me pone el móvil así
How many likes and you invite me to your house
Cuántos likes y me invitas a tu casa
How many likes and you invite me to the Epic
Cuántos likes y me invitas a la Epic
House npc
House npc
npc there's one sandwich
npc está uno bocadillo
yes What is it No thanks
sí Qué es No gracias
Ah at least show the car you
Ah por lo menos enseña el coche que te
bought no or
compraste no o
something I'll take it as a nlex a million
algo Lo tomaré como un nlex un millón
goodbye and of course I stayed like that for a bit
adiós y yo claro me quedé así un poco
because he caught me eating the ham like that but he's
porque me pillaba comiendo el jamón así
still in the same clothes
per está con la misma ropa todavía
back that he was wearing without trying the ham
espalda que llevaba sin probar el jamón
Since I left home and and of course I'm
Desde que me fui de casa y y claro yo de
joking whoever knows me knows that I
coña quien me conoce sabe que que lo
did it for humor in fact there were a lot of
hice de humor de hecho hubo un montón de
people who put it I stayed quiet like
gente que lo puso me quedé callado como
eating the sandwich and until then at the
comiendo el bocata y hasta que luego al
end of like a minute eh without
final de como un minuto eh sin
answering just eating the
contestarle simplemente comiendo el
sandwich I told him a million likes Well of
bocata le dije un millón de likes Pues
course it seems that it got confusing because I didn't
claro se ve que se ha liado porque no le
answer the kid and well I know that there has
contestaba al chaval y bueno que se que
been controversy on tiktok we already
ha habido controversia en tiktok ya
know how tiktok is  it's gone viral it's got
sabemos como es tiktok se ha viral lleva
like 600,000 likes in one day it's all
como 600,000 likes en un día enro el
the rage if you finally answered yes yes no but
revuelo si fin contestaste sí sí no pero
I mean what I want
o sea yo lo que quiero que entienda la
people to understand okay here we have to divide
gente vale aquí hay que hay que dividir
two things the first is
dos cosas la primera
also to think that it's my house like
e también tener pensar que es mi casa en
okay that I record you and tell you
plan que que vale que te grabe y te diga
How many likes to go to your house but it
Cuántos likes para ir a tu casa pero que
's my house like you can't
es mi casa en plan tampoco podéis
force me to invite everyone to
obligarme que invite a todo el mundo a
my house because if I tell the kid
mi casa porque si al chaval le digo que
yes the new trend is going to be
sí la nueva moda va a ser
Hey how many likes for your house How many
Eh cuántos likes para tu casa Cuántos
for your house and obviously because
para tu casa y obviamente porque a lo
maybe one comes come come one come
mejor a uno venga va venga uno venga
this one who has reached a million No maybe
este que ha llegado al millón No a lo
one is not going to mind
mejor a uno no le va a importar
inviting him one day come come come let
invitarlo un día venga va venga que se
a follower come to home who has
venga un seguidor a casa que ha
reached a million likes come on you
conseguido el millón de likes venga
know but of course This is already going away
sabes pero claro Es que esto ya se va
this is going to be several it's not going to be
esto ya lo van a ha ser varios ya no se
accepted anymore obviously
va a aceptar más evidentemente
okay this one was told the million
vale a este le ha dicho que el millón
but I'm telling you that this Now
pero ya te digo yo que esto Ahora lo van
several are going to do it and now when several do it
a hacer varios y ahora cuando lo hagan
and he doesn't  I answered, well, they'll
varios y él no conteste Eh pues lo lo
try to fool me, I'm sure 100% of my house
intentarán funar seguro 100% de mi casa
is the only place, the only place where
es el único sitio el único sitio en el
I rest a little, so that's why
que yo descanso un poquito entonces por
I was a little bit caught off guard because
eso me pillé un poco de prevenido porque
I was so calm with my
yo estaba tan tranquilo con mi bocata de
ham sandwich after 79 days without eating ham,
jamón después de 79 días sin comer jamón
all burst, 12 at night, Barcelona,
todo reventado 12 de la noche Barcelona
traveling, and they ask you that question, and
viajando y te sueltan esa pregunta y por
that's why the reaction was a bit like, what, what? So that
eso un poco la reacción de qué qué
on the one hand, and then the
Entonces eso por un lado y luego pues la
people who know me know that I simply
gente que me conoce sabe que simplemente
did it for humor, I don't understand all the
lo hice de humor no entiendo tanta
controversy that there is on tiktok that
controversia que que hay en tiktok que
people, I know that they do it to annoy,
la gente Yo sé que lo hace por [__] en
like, the comments that are, are
plan que los comentarios que son es
people who simply do it to annoy him.
gente que simplemente lo hace por [__]
But well, I wanted to, I wanted to comment on it.
Pero bueno quería quería comentarlo
Because surely the person who
Porque seguramente la persona que
comments something a minute later has forgotten
comente algo al minuto se le ha olvidado
that they have commented, you know, like, I think
que ha comentado sabes en plan yo creo
that's what it is, you know, I think, let's go, I
que eso sí que esc sabes yo creo vamos
think there were a lot of children too
yo creo que había mucho niño también
because it's not normal, I mean, well,
porque es que no es normal o sea bueno
people don't see either, but it's that
tampoco la gente ve pero es que de
we were really with The kid, I
verdad que estuvimos con El chaval le
'm going to talk to Paconi just in case, but of course
voy a hablar al paconi por si pero claro
the pony is over there, I was going to  to talk
el poni está por ahí le iba a hablar
about Fran's award when I
para lo del premio de Fran cuando yo me
left but they told me that he doesn't live in
fuera pero me dijeron que no vive en
Madrid
Madrid
paconi they told me that poni didn't live in
paconi me dijeron que poni no vivía en
Madrid I was going to talk to him in case he wanted to
Madrid le iba a hablar por si quería
give me the trophy if I take it to
darme el trofeo es si yo se lo llevo a
Fran minutes we all send Greetings
Fran minutos mandamos todos Saludos
Also it was just to take a photo to leave And
Además solo fue echar una foto irnos Y
honestly I also deal with a lot of
de verdad que yo trato también con mucha
famous people and precisely to tell you
gente famosa y precisamente decirte a ti
like u look like I went up to
como que u mira como que he subido a
see
ver
but the kid stands at the
pero es que el chaval se pone en el
airport waiting for all the
aeropuerto a a esperar a todos los
youtubers purito spursito spursito
youtubers purito spursito spursito
how many likes do you buy me the Play
cuántos likes me compras la Play
5o I'm going to buy the Play I don't have it for
5o vo comprar la Play no la tengo para
a photo even if it's just a photo spursito
una foto aunque sea una fotoo spursito
spursito damn what with the nonsense with the
spursito [__] que con la tontería con la
nonsense of the with the nonsense of the
tontería de los con las tonterías de los
like how many likes do you buy me the Play 5
lik cuántos likes me compras la Play 5
bro
bro
with the nonsense of the l who is
con la tontería de los l quién le está
asking people to see gres to you A
pidiendo a la gente a ver a gres a vos A
gres what does gref ask you How many likes do you
gres qué le pide gref Cuántos likes me
give me a ride in your tesla none I don't
das una vuelta en tu tesla ninguno no me
like tiktok but if  do you want me to give you
gustan los tiktok pero si quieres te doy
a hug dude okay come on let's go Give me a
un abrazo tío vale venga vamos Dame un
hug
abrazo
man [ __ ] at 7 in the morning already with
hombre [__] a las 7 de la mañana ya con
the tiktok I curse my mor gref
el tiktok me cago en mis mor el gref
is always nice right with people
siempre es Majo verdad con la gente
when they stop him he's always nice
cuando lo paran siempre es simpático
right
verdad
another Look at
otro Mira está
who is to forgive it's at 7 in the morning he has
quién perdonar es a las 7 de la mañana
taken gre
ha cogido a gre
host it's for the tit for the youtu
[__] es para el tit para el youtu
Sorry it's that I haa recognize you And
Perdón es que me haa reconocerte Y
that Hey G I just saw you and true
eso Oye G que te acabo de ver y verad
that I know you a ticho and a photo because
que te conoc un ticho y una foto porque
I am
soy
handsome but
hermosito pero
come on there is no more episode of this
vamos ya no hay más episodio de este
guy at the airport The truth is that
chico en el aeropuerto La verdad es que
I was having a good time the truth is
me lo estaba pasando bien la verdad es
that I was liking it seriously come on it's been
que me estaba gustando la serio vamos es
great this eh it's been
que ha sido buenísimo esto eh ha sido
great this eh I don't know what it is that the complete
buenísimo esto eh no sé qué es que todo
opposite or rather zero zero clar clear
lo contrario o sea cero cero clar claro
the comments were like
es que los comentarios eran rollo se me
an idol fell for me it's gotten higher
cayó un ídolo se le ha subido que se me
what it's gotten higher what it's been out
ha subido de qué que se me ha subido qué
there for 79 days I arrive in
que lleva 79 días por ahí fuera llego a
Spain I play Only Spanish and the first thing that  They
España toco Solo español y lo primero
ask to come to my house well
que me piden es venir a mi casa pues
man Well it's normal that I get mad But but oh
hombre Pues normal que me raye Pero pero
well no let's see The kid likes me I
bueno no a ver El chaval me cae bien o
mean no there's nothing against the kid
sea no no hay nada en contra del chaval
in fact The kid if he reaches the million
de hecho El chaval si llega al millón
Well he'll have to come to my house because
Pues tendrá que venir a mi casa porque
what is said is done and if not then I
lo que se dice se hace e si no pues me
would have shut my mouth and that's it But
hubiese callado la boca y ya está Pero
well I've already said it I will do it if it arrives
bueno ya lo he dicho Ya lo haré si llega
But but oh well guys please don't Do
Pero pero bueno eso chicos que por favor
n't get the trend of asking to
e no No cojáis ahora la moda de pedir
come to my house because I'm going to go
venir a a mi casa porque me voy a volver
crazy but it's funny because this
majareta pero es gracioso porque este
kid has come out a lot of
chaval m me ha salido un montón de
his videos and like wait People
vídeos suyos e como que espera Gente
come to spursito asked him for a Play the
llega a spursito le pidió una Play fue
video was very funny expit dio How many
muy gracioso el video expit dio Cuántos
likes if you buy me a Play 5 and exsito no no
likes si me compras una Play 5 y exsito
you haven't gotten many tits of him
no no te han salido muchos titos de él
because he doesn't have many tits let's see but if
porque no tiene muchos tit a ver pero si
literally he already took out the page here I
literalmente ya sacaba aquí la página o
mean many guys couldn't come out
sea muchos tios no te han podido salir
[ __ ] but it's that this guy from gre has
[__] pero es que este el de gre tiene
1,300,000
1,300000
you
tú
1300,000 let's
1300000
see  Many have not been able to get out You must have gone to
a ver Muchos no te han podido salir Te
see it and you must have gone
habrás metido a verlo y te habrás metido
to see what it
a ver qué es lo que
does, he said something like Play 5 if I don't
hace lo dijo algo rollo Play 5 si no lo
even have it, [ __ ]
tengo ni yo
gre he also said something to him and
cabrón gre le dijo también algo y le
asked him for a hug but well I simply
pidi un abrazo pero bueno simplemente
wanted to emphasize that, take advantage of this
quería recalcar eso aprovechar esta
chat to say it that that's it, they
tertulia para para decirlo que eso Ya
ask us something like If
está nos preguntan algo rollo Si
Netflix Amazon Prime came what am I and
viniese Netflix Amazon Prime qué s yo y
asked us to eat Around the World
nos pidiese comar La vuelta al mundo
for its platform would you sell it or
para para su plataforma la venderías o
not What is the question, I mean, what is the
no Cuál es la pregunta o sea cuál es la
answer, let's see, no, honestly,
respuesta a ver no sinceramente
sincerely adr, let go It depends, I
sinceramente adr suéltate Es depende yo
think, but more is that you have to answer this,
creo pero más es que esto tienes que
really, I have it clear, I mean, I wouldn't
real yo lo tengo claro o sea yo no me
look at the money unless they
fijaría en el dinero a no ser que me
offer me 100 million, you know if they
ofrezcan 100 millones sabes si me
offer me 100 million, then no, but I
ofrecen 100 millones pues no pero yo me
would look at whether if they come in,
fijaría en si entrando ellos va a salir
the content is going to improve or not Yeah,
va a mejorar el contenido o no Si a
yeah, net net pamos, if Netflix is going to come in
si net net pamos si va a entrar Netflix
and the series that they are going to make about the
y la serie que ellos van a hacer de la
trip around the world is going to be much worse, I would
vuelta al mundo va a ser mucho peor
never do it now he goes to Netflix and
jamás la haría ahora entra a Netflix y
says, Look, we're going to  to get that in
me dice Mira te vamos a conseguir que en
the destinations you can do more cool things
los destinos puedas hacer cosas más Guay
the videos are going to be better and everything and the
van a ser mejor los vídeos y todo y el
content is going to improve I
contenido va a mejorar
think Of course they would
creo Claro que lo
do it well
harían bueno
people until here for today I think it's
gente hasta aquí por hoy Yo creo que
pretty good now some other
está bastante bien ahora algún que otro
video for telesalseo for the lu and I'll
videíto para telesalseo para el luá y lo
leave it here you have a video here on this
dejo por aquí tenéis vídeo aquí en este
same channel okay you have a video
mismo canal vale tenéis un vídeo aquí
right here on this
mismo en este
channel from just a
canal de hace solo un
little while ago
ratte
just a
de hace solo un
little while ago okay There you have it
ratte vale Ahí lo
there you have it okay bomb Luisito
tenéis ahí lo tenéis vale bomba Luisito
and Ari lie cats tongues I was
y Ari miente lenguas de gatos tenía
right very
razón muy
good family How are you What's up
buenas familia Qué tal estáis Qué pasa
my kids pay attention because I have
mi chavalería atentos porque os Traigo
a bomb for you I'm here with Soul can you say hello
una bomba estoy aquí con Soul puedes
How are you all doing
saludar Qué tal cómo se encuentran todos
many thanks for inviting me again my
muchísimas gra por invitarme otra vez mi
dear Javi Thank you very much well is
querido Javi Muchas gracias bueno está
your house Soul is people that you listen to in the
tu casa Soul es gente que escucháis de
background of Soul from the world of Soul and they
fondo de Soul del mundo de Soul y se
are getting into it little by little well
está metiendo poquito a poco bueno
little by little no you are already into gossip
poquito a poco no ya estás metido en el
eh You are already into gossip
salseo eh Ya estás metido en el chisme
quite a bit yes yes I liked this
ya bastantito sí sí me gustó esto del
gossip Well it turns out that Soul  He
chisme Pues resulta ser que Soul me ha
contacted me this afternoon to tell me
contactado este mediodía para comentarme
that he had some pretty bombshell information
que tenía una información bastante bomba
And it seems that
Y es que parece ser que puede puede
Luisito is communicating and his girlfriend
podría que Luisito comunica y y su novia
Ari lied to us last night I'm not sure
Ari anoche nos mintier no sou parece ser
what's happening is that as you may have
lo que pasa es que como se habrán dado
noticed Those who are around a lot on
cuenta Quiénes anden mucho por ahí en
Twitter, since yesterday Luisito has
Twitter pues desde ayer Luisito ha
been
estado en
trending the truth is that the editor,
tendencias la verdad es que el editor
man, in a very short time he has taken out his
tío en muy poco tiempo se se ha sacado
[ __ ], he has made him super handsome, man, there
la [__] la ha hecho super guapo tío ahí
you see it okay There you see the
lo veis vale Ahí lo veis ustedes el
video You're going to see what Luisito lied to us about yesterday
vídeo Vais a ver en qué nos mintió ayer
So stop by there,
Luisito comunica Así que pasar por allí
rest, stop by Good night,
que descanséis paséis Buenas noches
gorgeous, rest okay See you
guapísimos Que descanséis Vale Nos vemos
tomorrow, probably or I hope so, a kiss
mañana seguramente o Eso espero un beso
guys
chicos